shutage: yoyo
yoyo_brobro: yoyo_brobro subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 6 months, currently on a 6 month streak!
shutage: more coq Kreygasm
equalizer_____: Hello form Russia
vlntnstts: no way you are alive
slow_manatee: oi bruv
eax_ebx: Еееее бой
hailstorm1422: 🃏
vossnorway800: What up
vlntnstts: привет лол
superman03: hola
LaheyFPS: What's today's agenda? @georgehotz
tonitcom: Hey bro
stephen422: hello from korea as well
imrtpk: <3
Ahxs: PogU
eax_ebx: Здесь одни русские?)
euranymous: Hey George
toolegit2quit_: Do you own an IDA license ?
EightyUser: Hello from the middle east
vossnorway800: Hello from Italy
Sylfine_Unreal: Hey boi:)
equalizer_____: Русские вперёд
the_shining: nice
yusufakcesme: Hello from Turkey!
thepooryaj: can we talk about self-driving cars? Kappa
鼻史: @georgehotz bro you didn't play ctf anymore ?
equalizer_____: А ещё знаете что самое интересное парни,мы их понимаем а она нас нет
sciacallo_98: Hello from italy too
yusufakcesme: Hello from Turkey
Cube_Is_Life20: @thepooryaj no
TopicOffic: @sciacallo_98 Ciaooooo ahhaha
sciacallo_98: LoL
TopicOffic: Hey yo Georgie how u doing
猎人杀手: ETA PS4 JB When? Kappa
poimaster91: Hello from Ohio
the_shining: LOL
thepooryaj: @Cube_Is_Life20 that was a joke
serohh: Hello from mountain view, CA !!!!!!!!!
superman03: can you help me with python?
devman12399: Hello from Egypt
hartator1: hot
toolegit2quit_: the fire is fire
Ziv0: LUL
euranymous: LOL
grizvok: grizvok subscribed at Tier 1.
trchaosTR: is it jailbroken ?
hartator1: i lov u
alxhotel: How big is your screen? Is hard to read the code :/
RenderMonkey: you need to get the beard back booyy!
the_shining: babay
grizvok: i love me some tendies
Cube_Is_Life20: Ayeeee tendies
Sylfine_Unreal: Why MacBook georgy
ragemaster999: IRL stream PogChamp
John_DiResta: ah better
hartator1: that what she says
greatpotatocat: Kreygasm
MrsEltim: hi
alxhotel: Thanks :)
Sylfine_Unreal: MacBook is bad
Orionmyth: selam aşkım HeyGuys
MonkaSupreme: MonkaSupreme subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 3 months, currently on a 1 month streak! damn son
euranymous: Next stream be like "Last Episode we made very geohot tendies"
speeddrawing101: Do you use a VPN? Just wondering @georgehotz
Cube_Is_Life20: george is a /pol/ack confirmed?
gazny: Think apple just enjoys not having closed source blobs in their kernel for osx
oMythra: Georgy boiii
MrsEltim: burada bir Türkün olacağını hiç düşünmemiştim
serohh: what’s in the tea??
euranymous: Binging With Babish has a great cooking channel
Erichmoraga: Chik-Fil-A FTW
the_shining: dalaodalao
yunusbcr: @MrsEltim Neden
stuartlz: Best life PogChamp
jay_al97: you know it's going to be a good day when @georgehotz gets onlne
gal40: Wow haven't caught one of your streams in a while
MrsEltim: genelde tr twitchinde boş yapılıyor
euranymous: Who else wants GEOHOT in NAHAMSEC's stream?
quelsarprime: freedom FTW
slimpimp007: high-key shots at LeBron
javadragoniv: america sucks anyway
EightyUser: gamers rise up
devm0d: Fuck yeah FREEDOM
haHAAXDDDDDD: that just made me think about terrys "similar" statement but i think its not twitch friendly so wont say anything Kappa
greatpotatocat: love and harmony bois Kappa
ggandy: Hey George, PERSONAL question: during hard days, how do you keep your mental health?
nightknight0000: yo yo yo yo yo yo
Erichmoraga: Quite the agenda for today... Freedom & chicken tender optimization.
grizvok: scary terry
serohh: Burda kac kisiyiz el kaldirin bakiyim☝🏻
gazny: Terry Davis?
webuser011: hello
haHAAXDDDDDD: yeah terry davis
speeddrawing101: let's play minecraft all day shroud200
MrsEltim: 1
yunusbcr: ben
Sylfine_Unreal: Yo mean the templeOS Terry
impact_FWT: omg man
gazny: I thought this was a no temple os stream
devm0d: Going to code up some freedom while eating my freedom fries
serohh: Haha guzeelll
yusufakcesme: türkler ses verin
Orionmyth: ses
Number___Nine: sup bros
euranymous: The temple os guy read shit loads of conspiracy shit
myaocat: whats up
MrsEltim: ses
yunusbcr: ses
serohh: ses
fafws321: ses
MonkaSupreme: ses
MonkaSupreme: ?
fafws321: Yohamına
JuisVen: is that lambda calculus?
Zeroman108: hi
javadragoniv: @Sylfine_Unreal I actually felt bad for terry during his end. Like the guy actually needed help and from what I know, he got none. It was sad. may he rest in peace
Number___Nine: rip Terry
yunusbcr: !uptime
bloodborne24: hes a basketball player i believe
MonkaSupreme: will this company sell hats and flamethrowers?
javadragoniv: terry with templeOS dude
ragemaster999: so how much rev did you get?
javadragoniv: yeye
spockshocks: terry is the guy who invented the programming gun to bring into whiteboarding interviews
grizvok: oh yeah this dude lol
euranymous: "><script>alert('wadabadbum')//</script>
the_shining: you zhongguo de ma
SlaterUSA: RIP Terry :(
Sylfine_Unreal: Yeah i actually liked that guy, in Germany he would get all the help he needed
beaverater: Rest in peace Terry. One of the true greats.
dongmuya: lmao templeOS
Number___Nine: it's all in asm lol
eaoruhgadfhjglajsdlfgj: yes
euranymous: temple OS is a meme
DasMastah: It is THE Terry
javadragoniv: yeah he's the one
Sylfine_Unreal: Its holy c its awesome
SlaterUSA: @georgehotz whatcha drinkin'?
Sylfine_Unreal: He wrote it himself
christian__james: we can t see because of the camera angle
dongmuya: the guy was legit out of his mind
eax_ebx: ахахахаха
sharmouta: don't bite your nail georgie!!
the_shining: what's his email
Sylfine_Unreal: Yeah That the terry but dont watch his vids on Stream XD
sirleeroyjenkins: Figured out how to prove true is not false: (if 1==1)
Sylfine_Unreal: Holy c is awesome
euranymous: His tea didnt have SUGAR it had COCAINE and his tea leaves were LSD contaminated
beaverater: No one has the right to cast a stone towards Terry until you write your own compiler and operating system that allows you to talk to God
haHAAXDDDDDD: yeah terry loved the n-word so u rly shouldnt atleast not with sound:D
javadragoniv: lmao offending code
christian__james: christian__james subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months! the best of the best
0twinshock0: whats you doing man ?
SlaterUSA: Terry was a bit schizo who went off on minorities etc.
euranymous: ignore terry @georgehotz
beylu_cs: he walks like a sims character
fafws321: @sirleeroyjenkins waow u are a genius
myaocat: wash hands
ragemaster999: i am mildly offended, but it may change at any point @georgehotz
gal40: He was a schizophrenic
myaocat: wash hands WutFace
dongmuya: Terry carpetted N-bombs like it was Vietnam all over again
fluzfluz: hello geooooooooorge ;-)
rapiddilemma: George what do you think of zsh instead of bash?
Sylfine_Unreal: @Beaverater 100% agree
euranymous: @sirleeroyjenkins Hey mate!
sirleeroyjenkins: Oh whats up
Sylfine_Unreal: Yes
Number___Nine: you also need half-float, bro
AtomicPandaAttack: I <3 YOU
euranymous: George would be a great guest in Ben's stream
Sylfine_Unreal: Its actualy genious
FlySociety2o9: LUL
beaverater: When God tells you that you should have a maximum screen resolution of 640 by 480, you don't question it, you just listen.
SlaterUSA: the rollercoaster stream of "ok this is great" - "ok no nononono"
f_karamazov: f_karamazov subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Sylfine_Unreal: @beaverater so true XD
FargioFarmani: lmao
Number___Nine: HolyC when
FurikuriYugi: Good morning
c252: hi
dongmuya: Terry = Even a broken clock is right 2 times in a day.
SlaterUSA: wasn't someone working on TempleOS, adding bells and whistles?
LaheyFPS: what do you recommend for maintaining a 4.0 GPA in college? @georgehotz
FurikuriYugi: Or aftermorning
Sylfine_Unreal: Yeah i believe george is gonna write holyC
SlaterUSA: @georgehotz what are u drinking?
roronoa_d_law: il mache de la glace là ?
nightknight0000: jesus h the ice chewing
SlaterUSA: asmr c
roronoa_d_law: nightknight0000 i know right
r4416: what kind of tea is that?
myaocat: how did we get from coq to templeos? Kappa
gazny: We are close to getting a speedrun of Eagle in temple os...
beylu_cs: hackerrank?
r4416: hackerrank
DasMastah: Hackerrank
MatiGoG: leetcode?
Number___Nine: look at kernel
FargioFarmani: George type of guy to eat two gummy bears together so they don't die alone.
sirleeroyjenkins: nice coq
JuisVen: but is it turing-complete?
flashingwolf122: stop trying to read his code, no one can comprehend terry's genius.. it's too much for us mortals
anup_kodlekere: hackerrank
myaocat: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tas0O586t80
Jewishrambo: The iso is 1mb for temple is
devm0d: Holy c.ocaine
serohh: leetcode lol
euranymous: LUL
Jewishrambo: Something like tht
shiftpgdn: Terry's code was written by divine right from god
不好意思: LUL
litesam: An example of towelroot Towelroot
gal40: The templeos bin is super small
beginbot: love the midi where my dawgs at
litesam: How to use Towelroot
thebastl: @georgehotz How much of your companies code is based on javascript?
sirleeroyjenkins: kinda looks like linerider
forkdb: Hi
SlaterUSA: @thebastl 2. Two.
MatiGoG: Jebated
dongmuya: snowman always eats you at the end of SkiFree
forkdb: First time viewer
euranymous: Terry Davis' tea was a perfect blend of pot, cocaine and lsd for maximum hallucinations and delusions
진정한모피어스: u're really good at this
beginbot: and we have successfully transitioned into ski free speedrunning!
beaverater: Have you ever wanted to embed fully rendered 3D Graphics into the middle of your code? The TempleOS IDE can do it.
f_karamazov: what about GOTO
electro_y0: LUL
forkdb: Am so excited to finally see you live
rapiddilemma: What's the timeline on these tendies ?
allesantosz: LUL
litesam: Towelroot explanation
SlaterUSA: skifree needs a vertical monitor
c252: FRACTRAN is a pretty awesome programming lang
thebastl: Did you start selling the subaru in a bundle with the comma hardware?
st47ik: nice gaming channel Kappa
gusfrehse: LUL
litesam: We need explanation about Towelroot
Cal3b123: hi George
gusfrehse: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
cat3009: hi
Sylfine_Unreal: @george So eazily distracted 😂😂
litesam: Guys ask to him about Towelroot[
MonkaSupreme: can I buy flamethrowers at baclspace.ai?
SlaterUSA: freedom from...?
forkdb: You are an inspiration
h3llofriend: @georgehotz just tell us humans how to become rich with limited ~110-120 IQ
euranymous: LUL
Number___Nine: backspace.ai sounds a bit like upwork, tbh
two_eight: freedom from your jobs when programs write themselves
st47ik: freedom is an illusion NotLikeThis
anup_kodlekere: is this a smart compiler or something?
roronoa_d_law: I have sensitive teeth to cold stop chewing ice please Keepo
JuisVen: Propositional logic
devm0d: Tell us more about backspace
danbokhari98: thats every cs student in a nutshell "I should know how to read this"
euranymous: ASMR vibes
FurikuriYugi: But illusions are free
litesam: Towelroot
Sylfine_Unreal: Freedom is when you write an AI who than code for you
st47ik: George where's the FPGA project at?
shiftpgdn: bro im crusing with a 65 IQ
two_eight: http in 2019 DansGame
sirleeroyjenkins: @georgehotz Do you do any bug bounty stuff like hackerone
litesam: An example about Towelroot
litesam: TOWELROOT
Avelansh: not even lets encrypt on the site
st47ik: LUL
beginbot: BibleThump
shiftpgdn: Damn that is a nice ass apartment, influencer life must be good.
valkerian97: @georgehotz are you still on bug bounty?
LaheyFPS: Kappa SURE
Bombapil0t: :(
0_______________________o: 6 LULW
serohh: CMU ALUMNI HEREE
jay_al97: you hack cars
grizvok: yes it is incredible
Number___Nine: hack da planet!
devm0d: How will backspace.ai become anything without crypto
geobitz: what do you call comma ai?
Bombapil0t: <3
MatiGoG: Kreygasm
Ziv0: LUL
devm0d: Don’t see BCH mentioned on backspace
0_______________________o: LUL
asaalgk: REAL
不好意思: LUL
h3llofriend: What do you think about Mr. Robot tv show? @georgehotz
two_eight: TRUE
nightknight0000: gotta make a living bro
0xBADBADBAD: how dare people want to make money :@
LaheyFPS: D: YES I AM
0_______________________o: D:
dr3wster: !hardware
SlaterUSA: they should make a Hackers 2 where the Angelina Jolie character is working for Symantec and has to deal with office misogyny and marketing drones asking if they could include just one more tracking pixel
Pryetranka: D: wtf
quelsarprime: label Asange
ggandy: <3
rsten: moon2W the chase for bugs is payment itself
鼻史: @georgehotz so you don't play ctf anymore
gabrielpolastrini: hello george
euranymous: I do bounties because its fun
gabrielpolastrini: hacking is boring nowadays, i quit working with it
gabrielpolastrini: i worked as a bug bounty hunter but i got tired
litesam: checkout http://twitch.tv/Naysayer88
LaheyFPS: basekit ball
0xBADBADBAD: Are we throwing in baseket ball?
SlaterUSA: Apple BaseKit. You thought macOS's beachball was bad?
FargioFarmani: @georgehotz what is your opinion about offshores in the tech industry?
serohh: Yoo dont chew ice and you won’t feel cold
Number___Nine: The RISC-V architecture is gonna change everything
Sylfine_Unreal: Yeah prbbly not
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz who do you respect the most, like in general, in science in engineerimg etc..?
Vinndy: they just make the game a consumable and try to break it down so anybody can get into it and make low risk high reward moves
forkdb: Big fan... you are an inspiration
0xBADBADBAD: Yes.
Erciks: yes
h3llofriend: How is it like to be a millionaire? Is there something that worries you nowadays?
Erciks: LULW
litesam: Jonathan Blow is streaming, he also created a compiler called Jai
SlaterUSA: art IS already outsourced, see those painters in China re-painting classic shit
programmer42: are you into logic programming nowdays ?
Number___Nine: we'll fix the art in the next release, bto
speeddrawing101: TRUEEEEE
MatiGoG: noone will LUL
Jewishrambo: Respects Linus but runs macOS Kappa
0xBADBADBAD: George is on some bullshit today LUL
0_______________________o: interesting perspective :)
svmihar: go back to the toq!
euranymous: But software engineers in third world countries are starving for opportunity
SlaterUSA: i'd buy a geohot stuffed formaldehyde shark
r4416: who needs Mr. Robot when you got this guy!
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz after all, pplz brain are just clever composition of atom, and once you can build brains, everyone can do art, everyone can do software
programmer42: Will go smoke weed and comeback. How long are you gonna be online today?
MatiGoG: if you cant tell it is a copy you pay the same
alexgorbatchev: mmmm... stuffed sharks
serohh: Nooo thats outsourcing
0_______________________o: PogU stealing John deer FW PogU
msalvy: Geohot, love OpenPilot!
Vinndy: george im working at a big corporate right now and feel like you just have to play their game and end up working for meaningless stuff, I don't like it what do I do
0xBADBADBAD: Wait wait we are taking bout tractors, we were just at baseket ball
persen: thanks I'll do that, brb becoming a billionare
litesam: Those third world countries doesn't respect startups, there is no place for a new startup at 3rd world countries.
gazny: Opensource firmware is legit, Have you looked into coreboot?
LaheyFPS: eryc200
grizvok: @Vinndy do you find no value in what you are doing?
mexeroserisback: I am a drill and I am thinking :)
r4416: what about the cost?
SlaterUSA: how many ritalins is our main man on today?
Number___Nine: OpenTractor
iskjmss: i wanna be drilled
grovsalt: acid > ritalin
hkisthebest: what are we doing today?
SlaterUSA: OpenBob?
Sylfine_Unreal: Most wanted Job in 2020: Building Tractors😂😂
0_______________________o: LUL
Ziv0: LUL
euranymous: your perspective is amazing man
Yeahsper: How high are you atm?
mexeroserisback: yes LUL
Keyeh: in the cloud i can be a drill
Avelansh: high on tea
kanogger: f o c u s e d
DahOne: idk man, kinda feels like you on crack...some thinking drill crack Kappa
MDSZilla: I guess we could say you're squirelling ?
devm0d: He’s on tea
MDSZilla: I cant even spell right
Vinndy: @grizvok at this point I don't know if I feel there's value on what I do or if the corporative bullshit they try to brain wash me with is working
SlaterUSA: tea alone does not do that.
extracheese42: NOT FALSE
devm0d: Tea will mess you up man, you don’t want none of that
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz you go to mars with musk's rockets once possible?
eduardoadf1: is coq = discrete math?
iskjmss: Tea with marijuana leaves is still tea
extracheese42: ANY TRUERS IN CHAT?????
r4416: What tea is that?
fluzfluz: green
Number___Nine: Yorkshire Tes
DahOne: @extracheese42 TRUEEE LULW
Bombapil0t: TwitchVotes
Number___Nine: Tea
euranymous: Is that the same tea that Terry Davis drank all of his life?
zacoaa: lmao u hear that
Pryetranka: could have done ASMR tho
extracheese42: TRUEEE @DahOne
hkisthebest: Anyone from taiwan in chat??
Keyeh: brb smoking weed
SlaterUSA: taiwan no.1
DahOne: @extracheese42 SQUADW? hell ya babay
litesam: What do you think about book Principles of compiler design; that big dragon book.
MDSZilla: You can play ADS as a Affiliate now.... https://dashboard.twitch.tv/u/georgehotz/stream-manager There's literally a button to run ads
zibranja: How would you debunk hollow earth theory
extracheese42: ANY NOT FALSERS IN CHAT??
programmer42: @Keyeh got some ?
extracheese42: @DahOne SQUADW bbb
SlaterUSA: any non-bots in chat?
grizvok: @Vinndy yeah I mean try to look at the positives of the job. Are you learning new skills that you can take somewhere else eventually
euranymous: me
beginbot: woah woah, bots are people too
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz any good movies or tv series you recommend?
MDSZilla: @georgehotz You can play ADS as a Affiliate now.... https://dashboard.twitch.tv/u/georgehotz/stream-manager There's literally a button to run ads
DahOne: @extracheese42 gordo later tonight with the squad ? ? Kappa
luxbock: if you are confused about what proof irrelevance means, consider the following:
luxbock: if you implement two sorting algorithms, say bubble sort and quicksort, mathematically they do the same thing, i.e. sort numbers
SlaterUSA: @MDSZilla so you're saying he should make money... WHILE HACKING?!?!?!
extracheese42: yes ofc!!! @DahOne
luxbock: however as programs they are clearly not the same, as they implement a different algorithm
alexgorbatchev: what are you doing today?
euranymous: 1 for using vim
MDSZilla: @SlaterUSA he's not hacking
MDSZilla: You can play ADS as a Affiliate now.... https://dashboard.twitch.tv/u/georgehotz/stream-manager There's literally a button to run ads
luxbock: if the type of your sorting program lives in SProp, you can't tell bubble sort and quicksort apart, because proof irrelevance means all proofs are the same, i.e. either your program works or it doesn't
litesam: USE E M A C S
Keyeh: any vimmers
litesam: E M A C S
Crocodillian: Is there a way to revert to op 6.0 and keep it that way? It performed best with my car
SlaterUSA: real hackers use nano
luxbock: if the type of your program lives in Type, you can tell a quicksort apart from bubble sort, because the proofs/programs are different
Vinndy: @grizvok yeah I mean I could learn AWS and that definitely makes me more hireable but for what to just do the same meaningless stuff at a different company
euranymous: VIM is life
quelsarprime: lol Slacker
serohh: Spacemacs💪🏻💪🏻
Crocodillian: vim and nano are both good, but i like vim because it's modal
SlaterUSA: spacemacs is pronounced 'Spack emacs"
micos7: Any programmer believing in the absolute true hasn`t seen JavaScript true table
MDSZilla: @georgehotz You can play ADS as a Affiliate now.... https://dashboard.twitch.tv/u/georgehotz/stream-manager There's literally a button to run ads show us some ads ;)
Crocodillian: I recommend symbolic logic philosophy course at any college
gazny: I declined a job because of dress code once
Number___Nine: FAANG
Keyeh: have you listen to Jesus in King by Kanye West georgehotz
euranymous: stop working for a man
mexeroserisback: business development LUL
beginbot: but the free snacks!
msalvy: What do you mean by not creating value? Can you explain more
cat3009: googleprojectzero is about money or culture?
Number___Nine: FPGA trading for lyfe
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz you mean 'math people will replace mad people' ?
MDSZilla: You can play ADS as a Affiliate now.... https://dashboard.twitch.tv/u/georgehotz/stream-manager There's literally a button to run ads :P
SlaterUSA: @MDSZilla why do you keep spamming that...
swsh: Hey, is it Coq? Why not Lean, I heard it's strictly better.
MDSZilla: SlaterUSA so he can make money LUL
mikewow3: geohot is streaming
micos7: Are you on hackerone?
msalvy: What do you think about OpenAI?
posixninja: amen
Crocodillian: script kiddies
Vinndy: @georgehotz i share that vision but I don't feel like I have the resources to just drop it, it's not Facebook or Google, it's "rainforest" (don't wanna name it) but I still feel like it's meaningless
kito__: hello
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz still fan of yudkovsky?
msalvy: lmaoo
euranymous: Takeaway:Don't work for the man
JuisVen: Do you want us to never work for others and make our own companies
caslecasle: !uptime
mikewow3: ive concluded the singularity is fake news
MDSZilla: Affiliates can now run ads George its in your dashboard... when you open twitch dashboard click the blue bar on top
mikewow3: softbank is off a bean
beginbot: LUL
Crocodillian: i'm just booty chasing
mexeroserisback: yes I am creating value for my ceo to buy another villa Kappa
trajenx: i came hear to learn programming not economics
micos7: being a parasite
SlaterUSA: @MDSZilla jfc stop it already holy hell
Number___Nine: additional business value
Attlantiz_: is that coq
warpoit: same
Crocodillian: my value for the world is giving love to chubby girls
coProof: I miss old George when he wasn’t always trying to prove something FeelsBadMan
Keyeh: @trajenx you can to the wrong channel then lmao
grizvok: i love the tangents george goes on
Julll: draw.io
erichtp: draw.io
byte_baron: ms paint
Jannnik: draw.io
purplepinapples: yes @Attlantiz_
MDSZilla: SlaterUSA You were saying?
tornpaperyoyos: that true is not false
forkdb: Big fan... you are an inspiration to me to do better programming
Jewishrambo: Draw.io
celiezz: learning economics from someone running on venture capital xD
SlaterUSA: @MDSZilla i was saying, it's weird that u keep spamming that stuff
th3_maj0r: paint > draw.io
tornpaperyoyos: hes tired of you always wanting to prove if true is not false and all that
coProof: You’re proving if something is not true or false
MDSZilla: SlaterUSA I didnt mention @SlaterUSA in the message so it wasnt for you :)
Crocodillian: Untitled diaphragm
Crocodillian: modus tollens
anup_kodlekere: the right line is thicker than the left
Keyeh: Kappa
tornpaperyoyos: @coProof damn it he saw yoursz not mine lol
thebastl: @georgehotz Do you like ruby on rails?
shaymin_fakezz: 5Head
Kustex: socialism
Keyeh: big brain idea, worked in russia
MDSZilla: I think we had a similar discussion based on TedTalks etc
caslecasle: Jesus christ i havent watched this many ads since the super bowl
gazny: You hire them and give them discounts to get them to give that positive feedback loop
coProof: @tornpaperyoyos lol
Crocodillian: geohot you're such a casual entrepreneur
coilru: ok give me salary ill be your customer wut
andrewbhatfield: @Kustex that's the dumbest notion of what socialism is i've ever seen
Big_America_: hello twitch police, george is talking about MMT and i am afraid.
Keyeh: in this channel: streamer explaining planned economy
tornpaperyoyos: you lost me
coProof: Can you acquire your twitch subs?
Bombapil0t: follow him on instagram guys
beginbot: as long as you are growing you never need to make money!
euranymous: If they sue our georgie again we gonna tickle their lawyers to death
Nequa27: FiveHead
Crocodillian: government contracts is where it's at
mexeroserisback: Customers = C
beginbot: what if we could create the customers??? instead of acquire
euranymous: LUL
YouPowerRush: sikk
mikewow3: we're heading into the deep waters now
thyssen: LUL
MDSZilla: So they consume the product lets make a Food Company Kappa
gazny: Theory of cashback no?
quelsarprime: George I'm drowning... you just broke my brain.
Keyeh: 5Head
Crocodillian: ponzy scheme
Kustex: haha mmt in full force
hkisthebest: this is pyramid scheme
a_caspar: CoolStoryBob ahhhh
tornpaperyoyos: "heres another scam we can do" - george hotz 2019
eduardoadf1: PogChamp
coilru: why dont you start by paying all of your viewers for watching you Kappa
le0n_: ah i missed the begining
msalvy: George "take a look at this diagram that explains as scam" Hotz
0xBADBADBAD: This version of Lex Luthor is weird
Big_America_: We could build a sailboat and power it by blowing into the sails from the helm.
iagia: but they don't want the money, they want the damn product
beginbot: HeyGuys
thyssen: good idea
Crocodillian: not a scammer LOL
Keyeh: LUL
filipeoliveiraa: Kappa
Pryetranka: Kappa
roronoa_d_law: qu'est ce qu'il raconte
coilru: Kappa
eduardoadf1: george school of economics
gazny: This is a Multi Layer Marketing
coProof: Acquire us
speeddrawing101: So when are we proving true is not false? @georgehotz
mikewow3: they say you can buy revenue
Crocodillian: Georgeconomics
le0n_: oh MLM
iagia: customers show up for the product
YouPowerRush: sikk circle bruh
mexeroserisback: Why not buy the investors too
le0n_: lol
Vinndy: @georgehotz you mentioned on lex fridman that you went to Carnegie Mellon to see what you had missed out and said that the courses were great but didn't mention if after that you felt like you had actually missed out on something, how do you feel like about a degree after that?
euranymous: Social engineering skills *insert mushroom cloud here*
Number___Nine: Blade Runner
tornpaperyoyos: tf are u talking about
roronoa_d_law: speeddrawing101 already done
iagia: they don't show up for money
Bombapil0t: iq > 9000
ensareray99: How can you be this sure all customer wants to work for you?
le0n_: thanks m8
Keyeh: buy me george
FUSiONPlays: succ
hkisthebest: @georgehotz how do you prove true is not false?
iagia: that's NOT a good idea at all
searchingforlife: comma ai strategy leaked by gpt2
MDSZilla: george are you using the vanilla terminal of Mac or a different one?
Crocodillian: false premise always results in false conclusion
coilru: @georgehotz have you heard about terry davis (temple os), some of your things resemble what he said :D
roronoa_d_law: print(true == false) outputs false so this proves true is not false. right ?
Tyl3r44: is this prolog?
MDSZilla: False is a set with no items what if the set is supposed to be empty?
tornpaperyoyos: fucking temple OS LUL LUL LUL
0_______________________o: STALLING cause bad LUL
gal40: Maybe a lot
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz maybe ternary logic will be a better choice for your project ;) ?
msalvy: George "get a load of this scam" Hotz
Number___Nine: formally proven TempleOS
ragemaster999: maybe there is some code on stackoverflow
coilru: templeOS BlessRNG
caslecasle: @georgehotz have you sold an Subaru harnesses
MDSZilla: Sorts? Ascending or Descending thats all I know Kappa
Number___Nine: Monoind in the category of endofunctors, bro
devm0d: When George pushes his finger on his forehead that’s his Go button when he figures the hard shit out
fghoekstra79: George. are hij aware you're a cast reader?
Zacharycht: yes
fghoekstra79: i'm half way and he's already finished!
luxbock: @georgehotz consider two sorting algorithms, say quicksort and bubble sort. they do the same thing mathematically i.e. sort numbers, but as computer programs they are different
iagia: I can't spend any brain cycles on this channel any more... SEE YA
prvk3: I did not understand a single world
prvk3: word*
rhizomia: О, вижу SF и HoTT
luxbock: if you write your sorting program in SProp, you can't tell quicksort and bubble sort apart, because proofs in SProp are proof irrelevant, which means that either you have a working program or you don't
ensareray99: Which lang. is that? Python?
rhizomia: coq
Am4teur: you kinda cute
luxbock: if your sorting algorithm lives in Prop/Type, the proof/program of your type are data, which means you can tell them apart
Number___Nine: ensareray99 some sort of Coq
luxbock: I am not trolling, this is what it means
tornpaperyoyos: LUL LUL LUL
forkdb: Please read Big fan... you are an inspiration to me to do better programming
devm0d: Oh dang, Am4tuer wants your nuts
tornpaperyoyos: definitely trolling
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz after youre done with comma.ai, will you work on hacking our world simulation?
luxbock: @georgehotz SProp is useful when you want to proof properties of your programs but not have to bear the cost of those proofs at runtime, this is because the proofs are irrelevant, they can be erased after compilation has completed
Harm133: what is twitchcoq ?
zenkai_oogway: @jagger_rsw dont talk about that here
marezino: :) :) :) :) :)
Number___Nine: time to order food
Bombapil0t: sellout cmonBruh
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz what do you want to be coached about?
gindalf: DO IT! somebody please
devm0d: You should just sell tea on your website
Sarkin_dota: 15 minutes? DansGame
gal40: What about 50 Zimbabwe Dollars?
anup_kodlekere: thats smart
MonkaSupreme: 200 an hour
tornpaperyoyos: 50 bucks for 15 minutes?
0_______________________o: memes incoming LUL
nightknight0000: lmao
Bombapil0t: okok i see
YouPowerRush: tap tap tap
Sarkin_dota: Dansgame
forkdb: Please read Big fan... you are an inspiration to me to do better programming
FargioFarmani: paste your bitcoin address
luxbock: @georgehotz again consider quicksort vs. bubblesort, and a program that has to deal with the behavior of those algorithms at runtime. if you only need to reason about the mathematical behavior (i.e. that they do the right thing), then SProp is enough and it's probably better because you don't pay a runtime cost. if you need to reason about the behavior of the algorithms, you can do so by working with proofs of Prop/Type
Iliftmymousealot: i can I paypal you 50 dollars without coaching session
Vinndy: somone paypal him LUL
FargioFarmani: @georgehotz paste your bitcoin address
jagger_rsw: I'm poor, so only 50 ukrainian hryvna?
eduardoadf1: are donations enabled?
forkdb: Please read Big fan... you are an inspiration to me to do better programming
devm0d: Paste your private bch address again
devm0d: When seadoo?
Number___Nine: jagger_rsw I won't even pay you 50 rupees for 50 hryvna :)
YouPowerRush: haha
eduardoadf1: 1 dollar LUL
Abo7atm: youre taking donations?
forkdb: Please read Big fan... you are an inspiration to me to do better programming
tornpaperyoyos: "im really into scams" - George Hotz 2019
gal40: Donate to teamtrees instead.
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz so maybe you want to give us 50 $? :)
Number___Nine: 1m2019.com
cheleclol: how many hours you sleep a day?
Mariosavitch: pyramid schemes?
knysh: bitconnect LUL
beginbot: Can't wait for the episode of America Greed with @georgehotz
luxbock: @georgehotz if you are familiar with the Curry-Howard correspondence between proofs/programs, it only applies when you are working with proof relevant types (Types) instead of SProp. proofs in SProp are not programs, they are just proofs
eduardoadf1: bitconeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeect
Abo7atm: can we buy equity in backspace tho?
JuisVen: Like athene
Quad___lol: bitcoonnnnnnneeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeek
forkdb: Please read Big fan... you are an inspiration to me to do better programming
msalvy: Geoge "get a load of this fat scam" Hotz
my_curiosity: how is any crypto currency not a scam?
MonkaSupreme: you should check out athenelive crypto scam. he said it was a scam from the beginning
gindalf: @georgehotz are you behind backspace.ai?
tag_gaming_stream: Wow, I have been following your comma ai archive videos all summer, I been waiting for a live stream, this is awesome you are a legend George!
devm0d: You’re close to Mexico now, lots of import opportunity there
beginbot: yes @gindalf
prvk3: @georgehotz dude just get @luxbock in a call, and then u can give him 50
averagesizepens: stop running ads you rich boy
ggandy: I love to hear your way of thinking / philosophy , do you ever consider starting a podcast?
Number___Nine: fedcoin scam
Mariosavitch: "were going to rip you off..."... "awesome, how do I join?" @georgehotz
luxbock: @georgehotz you are talking about the difference between extensional vs. intensional equality
DasMastah: Equivalance needs context, right?
96terrax96: gucioHead
Iliftmymousealot: is kickstarter a scam?
programmer42: can you start writing code pls?
devm0d: geohotcoin
devm0d: I’ll be an advisor
beginbot: I would transfer all my dogecoin to geohotcoin
luxbock: quicksort and bubble sort are extensionally equivalent, in that they have the same outputs for the same inputs, but they are not intensionally equal, because their definition/algorithm are different
data_day_life: ^
Quad___lol: pyramids are a scam
gal40: Could you explain why the halting problem is a problem for your equality operator?
tag_gaming_stream: Wow, I have been following your comma ai archive videos all summer, I been waiting for a live stream, this is awesome you are a legend George!
JuisVen: Every sorting algorithm is extensionally equivalent then
forkdb: Please read Big fan... you are an inspiration to me to do better programming
yoloman1343: are you ever going to tour george
amratesh: Sorry I'm late
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz is it possible to use ML to break crypto, i.e. to create a model which will e.g. create sha collisions with enough training?
guldPRIVANN: Hello :D How is life everyone ? :D
MonkaSupreme: Bogosort
yoloman1343: i would unironically pay big $$ to see u rap live
Number___Nine: kolmogorov complexity
tornpaperyoyos: NotLikeThis
kishan0505: !pc
euranymous: Is it the FBI?
YouPowerRush: wash hands
blankinator85: monkaS
amratesh: I see you're not playing on hard anymore.
JuisVen: It's the toilet
baxteriia: thats a 1000$ chair
tag_gaming_stream: If someone is able to hack his obs install python script into his paypal login and intitalize a donation animation you win
gal40: Could you explain why the halting problem is a problem for your equality operator?
Sarkin_dota: @yoloman1343 you could instead pay 50$ for a 15 minute life coaching session, and then ask George to rap like your life depends on it
Number___Nine: typing ASMR
yoloman1343: holy shit that's brilliant @Sarkin_dota
beginbot: Life coaching in the form of a fire Freestyle
Big_America_: past streams paywalled PogChamp
gindalf: but the haulting would be an internal property, no?
yoloman1343: george hotz rap show when
gal40: But we know the halting program couldn't exist in the first place - so comparing it to another program isn't an option
jagger_rsw: does it make sense to use ML to break crypto, e.g. to train a model which will produce sha collisions or so?
beginbot: but then where will you sit??
stalys_: $5k chair PogChamp
beginbot: you can't program without a chair
tag_gaming_stream: TURN ON DONATION!
tornpaperyoyos: bogo sort is the best sorting algorithm
beginbot: 2 chairs!
beginbot: Holy shit you are rich
yoloman1343: george were you really bottom 5 in your class?
amratesh: @big_america_ you can watch them on YouTube
filipeoliveiraa: or sit on the floor Kappa
amratesh: Comma Ai archives
data_day_life: those chairs are extensionally equivalent
Big_America_: then youtube knows what i watch
tag_gaming_stream: Comma Ai Arhcives are king
JuisVen: Is rich, sits on a 5$ chair
eax_ebx: ok, how to be rich?
hkisthebest: Do you code with vim in java?
anup_kodlekere: new hoodie?
SnakeOneMLG: @hkisthebest he doesnt code in java
zoki_macola: when did the stream started
MDSZilla: Georgehotz 100% Premium Merch coming soon Kappa
euranymous: !uptime
Quad___lol: its easy to get rich...just have no morals
MonkaSupreme: i'd buy merch
amratesh: @georgehotz when am I getting the Backspace emote we talked about?
zenkai_oogway: @georgehotz thoughts on kanye's new album?
cozinn: Just WHYYYY
data_day_life: 1hr, 1 minute ago
ragemaster999: are they sure they are not trolling?
hkisthebest: @SnakeOneMLG any reasons?
tag_gaming_stream: @Quad___lol That is 100% true, sad, but true throw your morals out rich immediately
eax_ebx: ok, I have not morals, what's next?
SnakeOneMLG: @hkisthebest he really doesn't like the idea of the language I think
MonkaSupreme: mylBbrain
Number___Nine: eax_ebx go sell out
luxbock: @georgehotz if you want to learn dependently typed programming, the book The Little Typer is a book written in the style of a childrens book, but it talks about the types of things you read on the Coq manual
amratesh: @eax_ebx sell a kidney
tag_gaming_stream: Find girls to make porn, pay them almost no money, upload the videos make money off royalties forever off their content they kill themselves in 5 years for ruining their lives and having no careers and you make money forever, boom solved
luxbock: it's an interesting juxtaposition
tag_gaming_stream: no morals
tag_gaming_stream: craigslist
knilecrack: wsupp
knilecrack: long time no see
recursive_x: filter through x amount of logic gates to understand binary input and output and if its a perfect opposite then it is not false but also true
tag_gaming_stream: Use recursion though
lyricrush: 4Head
amratesh: Geohot backspace emote!
JuisVen: Do you enjoy software engineering or ML
Number___Nine: can you use coq to prove simulation theory?
tag_gaming_stream: @eax_ebx Read my method and he left and is now posting in craiglist to get girl hah
eduardoadf1: can someone explain to a brainlet what coq has to do with sorting? also, in my head, coq is like discrete math coded and tested(?)
amratesh: Simulation hypothesis is unfalsifiable
Quad___lol: I have a problem no AI can help me with. I have been with a girl for 3 years, now she has problem getting a visa and 2 other girls here want me. What to do :/
dMunkei: become homosexual
dMunkei: dodge all the girls
grizvok: he alreaady is
Lazylion2: @Quad___lol polygamy
Number___Nine: have you seen Joe Rogan with that simulation hypothesis Swedish guy?
euranymous: arrange a foursome in the country where the girl who couldnt get a visa lives
luxbock: @eduardoadf1 I was using sorting algorithms as an example to illustrate a point, but the word `Sort` in the Coq documentation has nothing to do with sorting, it is more like a container/class/collection
tag_gaming_stream: You need to use the distributed model
knilecrack: merry her in her country and then she can move in
eduardoadf1: @luxbock i see, thanks
knilecrack: marry*
luxbock: @georgehotz you are thinking of Russel's paradox
jagger_rsw: @euranymous with bostrom, he's somewhat famous
data_day_life: what's the complement of the Universal Set
data_day_life: ya
Ipkstef: What're we working on today?
data_day_life: exactly
berghyfps: category: Basic programming
berghyfps: what is happening
euranymous: @jagger_rsw I lost track of what i said, what are you replying to?
recursive_x: if a set of all sets cannot be contained then all other sets can
luxbock: fun fact: The Halting Problem, Russel's Paradox, Cantor's Theorem, Nash Equilibrium are all instances of Lawvere's Fixpoint Theorem
luxbock: https://arxiv.org/pdf/math/0305282.pdf
Number___Nine: TempleCoq
LaheyFPS: do programmers get girls? @georgehotz
swsh: Here is the Agda proof for reference: https://agda.github.io/agda-stdlib/Data.Bool.Properties.html#13515
grizvok: Yes we do
byte_baron: @LaheyFPS watch the social network, of course they do
ViktorTV: done with comma?
asaalgk: tldr on Lawvere's Fixpoint Theorem?
Vinndy: so you're saying you will be done with comma
Abo7atm: ML as in Machine Learning?
euranymous: @LaheyFPS you mean: Do the creatures above the food chain get a chance to mate?
luxbock: @georgehotz if you want to take the long way, start studying Category Theory now :)
scatterp2: @georgehotz can I ask you a question about aslr ?
luxbock: I recommend the book Seven Sketches in Compositionality, it is freely available online
luxbock: it is for "applied CT", i.e. it has real world examples of applications
Zacharycht: paradigm
celiezz: how will coma become profitable exactly?
grizvok: ive been thinking of literally EVERYTHING like that recently. every class, every file, etc. what are the inputs what is the desired output
euranymous: whats ML?
paradox109: machine learning?
Number___Nine: ocaml
AdvanceCoder4Life: What is your real goal, George? Are you creating an app or evaluating an algo using code?
zoki_macola: Did anyone manage to create a mini-universe with cellular automata? With some simple particles and their interactions?
swsh: Have you seen Bartosz Milewski's stuff on category theory?
scatterp2: it allows you to apply categorys to stuff there's a very large maths book about it I thought it might work well for fuzzing
Zacharycht: isnt that called overstanding
Ipkstef: @georgehotz has CommaAI been using real-state data in its simulator and if so have you started training with that dataset?
Zacharycht: when you fully overstand
programmer42: brb I'll take a quick shower
tfue_is_dog_shit: can you prove 0 is 1
Number___Nine: zoki_macola John Conway did
grizvok: that makes sense
Keyeh: ml is glorified statistics
Quad___lol: machine learning and AI is just advanced statistics ...
jagger_rsw: so ML is like natural evolution (program as DNA)
swsh: true is not false is True by definition of "not"
Keyeh: all nature physical phenomena can be posed as a optimization/minimzation problem
dawgwhisper007: category theory simplified - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jBkO1eerU8A
c19946: Hey people buy Geo's Subaru sh**s it's great I promise...
iTeQo_: F this shit. I‘m switching to Minecraft stream instead
jagger_rsw: it fits your definition, life is a massively parallel search process operating on a biological computer immersed in slightly salty water
scatterp2: there's a book higher topos theory which helps explain category maths
luxbock: @scatterp2 I think topos theory is great once you already know some CT, but if you are intimidated by regular CT, then topos theory is probably the worst possible area to start from
tfue_is_dog_shit: talk is cheap, show me the code
Aerdayne: monkaHmm
vave2_: pajaScoots
strminftr: @tfue_is_dog_shit do you even brain?
Jewishrambo: Kreygasm
scatterp2: @luxbock geo could handle it I suppose
Kimx_: Plants are whores.
Aerdayne: I spay my dna over everything too like plants
Quad___lol: can you not say word sex? my mum always looks at me
byte_baron: ^
byte_baron: please stop the naughty talk !
asaalgk: having the option is a better word than choice
Jewishrambo: lol
byte_baron: no randy talk please fella !
knilecrack: you can if bitches can show tits you can say sex
zoki_macola: :D
mexeroserisback: LUL
jagger_rsw: so, what's the search function that human brain uses to solve problems? Like going through known patterns and applying them one after another until something works?
Number___Nine: Quad___lol so Coq is OK but SEX isn't? :))
FargioFarmani: Hi mom!
Zacharycht: bye
Keyeh: if we can say coq we can say secs
Zacharycht: sex
Number___Nine: seqs
sultantw: hyper active kid
Bitcoin__: Bitcoin__ subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 8 months, currently on a 8 month streak! Love your content
scatterp2: @luxbock what's your background do you hack ?
luxbock: @scatterp2 topos theory is categorical abstraction on higher order logic, which means in terms of abstractness it ranks just about as high as any subject I can think of, except of course for higher-topos theory :)
luxbock: @scatterp2 I'm just an internet addict
kektobiologist: whats going on i dont understand stream title
Keyeh: prove it with coq
asaalgk: sounds like from schmidhuber
mexeroserisback: Why should I understand it, I just download Sklearn 4Head
xrealyy: nice coq
prvk3: LMFAOO
paradoxeryy: i guess they meant in nature, everything's a sum of smaller parts
mexeroserisback: its a metaphorical statement
Quad___lol: not sure if mr trump would like it
Number___Nine: PhD. in Coq
eax_ebx: mb it's mean superposition?
kektobiologist: im too 3Head for this channel
hideoto: hambHey
asaalgk: i remember reading the reason witty humor is funny is because it compresses information and we like that
xrealyy: why proving something obvious?
slArkBig: you have to put metaphor in order to finish this paper
el_Razor: its a Sayl chair ?
prezk0: @georgehotz what's the point of all this? are you trying to win the hutter prize?
spenceman4311: filler garbage
Keyeh: because mathematicians are not real people 4Head
jagger_rsw: are you seeing a chance for training models with ML to prove math conjectures in the future?
murkythunder: N OMEGALUL
hideoto: Most journals will probably reject too short (human wordy) papers
vave2_: N squadOmega
mexeroserisback: I think its a problem with the subject itself. The authors are trying to connect the math to real world examples but it does not really make any sense since the math is way too abstract
Kimx_: haha love this guy. I always feel the same way
knilecrack: this is easy to understand with structures and compositional.
Keyeh: you don't have the pre-requisites to understand this paragraph 4Head
averagesizepens: install pre-requisites please
scatterp2: there's a video I can suggest
murkythunder: gender KappaPride
mexeroserisback: Maybe check Terence Tao's website? He explains math extremely well
scatterp2: largely it's complicated all the way
ViktorTV: I mean you are a college dropout so it's hard for you to comprehend. Kappa
CondomsWontFit: LUL
dawgwhisper007: lol
Ya_mums_granny: LUL
whichtom: I mean you're reading a pub, which inherently uses exclusive language because academia is wack
tunacan_man: LUL
Keyeh: WutFace
Number___Nine: ResidentSleeper
dawgwhisper007: oh
spenceman4311: pseudo-intellectual bullshit lol
tunacan_man: the capitalist paradigm of consensus LUL
tornpaperyoyos: that sounds like a bunch of nonsense LUL
averagesizepens: it is, it's all hegel's fault
murkythunder: why u gotta do jordan peterson like that
jagger_rsw: you should read about the ontological argument, it's the same type of mind-bender from XI century :)
luxbock: @georgehotz CT arose from the need to unify different areas of mathematics, it is often described as the mathematics of mathematics, which explains the language. because of this it has a very steep learning curve, but once you get there you have a very nice birds eye view on many topics outside of mathematics (such as theorem proving, machine learning, dynamical systems etc.)
mexeroserisback: @georgehotz there is a math paper generator as well LUL
veeniii: humans also generate a lot of nonsense, no need for a computer ^^
anup_kodlekere: your webcam blinks
dawgwhisper007: what is a markoff chain
jaalle: Marx was right
purplepinapples: markov chain
strminftr: got it, thx
ViktorTV: good old hmms
swsh: KarlMarxov chain
paradoxeryy: the more they lean into abstraction the lower the truthfulness of the statement, since it's building on other 'can't prove in reality' stuff, hence y math > social sciences
xrealyy: you want win noble or what?
xrealyy: *nobel
jagger_rsw: in literature
Number___Nine: category theory ASMR
prafaeltsantos: whats is @georgehotz favorite linux distro? :D
paradoxeryy: nobel doesn't award math accomplishments, The Fields Medal is your math nobel
Number___Nine: prafaeltsantos Arch
knilecrack: mac os
luxbock: @georgehotz it means absolute value
swsh: it is absolute value
eax_ebx: btw I use arch
xrealyy: @paradoxeryy
dawgwhisper007: pipe character is to indicate absolute values
shlver: math NotLikeThis
sane72: distance is absolute value of the difference
Number___Nine: meth
prafaeltsantos: @Number___Nine hoooww boy, he really likes difficult things....
xrealyy: this is what happens when you code your entire life
Number___Nine: prafaeltsantos there was a stream of geohot installing arch
mexeroserisback: but it is true in the prime field Z_p
kilo_atl: Love that noise
luxbock: @georgehotz also negation does not preserve order, 3 <= 4 but it is not the case that -3 <= -4
GENETISKTLITEN: Finally you are online! Is the HHKB2 worth it @georgehotz
prafaeltsantos: @knilecrack nice try Tim Cook
jagger_rsw: ha.. metric.... you should use imperial
strminftr: yes it is
anup_kodlekere: yes
asaalgk: probably yeah, if its distance
tunacan_man: LUL
minmaxy: yes, it's "preserve the distance"
mexeroserisback: Its the absolute value because the function is in R
Number___Nine: Marx foesn't approve imperial
Number___Nine: *doesn't
sane72: yes
mexeroserisback: but you could consider any space where distance is defined differently
s4ngim3d: Hi people
DrPacMan: DrPacMan subscribed with Twitch Prime.
prafaeltsantos: @Number___Nine that must be a fun one, I am watching some old ones, but i haven´´´ t reach that one
Number___Nine: prafaeltsantos yeah it is very funny
sane72: F(x]
sane72: Just
DrPacMan: hey
sane72: F(x)=x-1
turboooooo1: George this is some cool stuff
sane72: preserves distance but not the sum?
Number___Nine: refucktoring
LaheyFPS: D: RUDE
FUSiONPlays: D:
mexeroserisback: LUL
razr22: D:
vave2_: true
prvk3: I'm trying my best :'(
averagesizepens: thx my dude
FUSiONPlays: that would be hella PogChamp
swsh: BibleThump
scatterp2: that's ml
twiggy_io: Might be a dumb question refactoring on what abstraction level? Like CPU level?
jagger_rsw: I tink Ill go and eat some pierogi
alexgorbatchev: in Soviet Russia code refactors you
grizvok: its a good book
Number___Nine: probably a program could factor out some snippets into funtions, but I don't think it can do a proper refactorinmg
swsh: to much power, it's just AGI
ensareray99: @georgehotz Where did you learn use coq and why?
lemonboxed: its a real fake word
GENETISKTLITEN: Would you recommend to pickup a HHKB2? @georgehotz
grizvok: talking keyboards are a bannable offense
grizvok: is*
zoki_macola: started playing with it ;D
jagger_rsw: Das Kapital
speeddrawing101: I would buy that
Number___Nine: AR headset pls
UrWifeMyKids: NLP Pog
MonkaSupreme: where can i buy it
Number___Nine: what keyboard Terry used?
hideoto: That's actually a Russian propaganda technique
m2g_ro: for automated refactoring to work, I think the machine must understand the domain model so that it produces code that makes it easier for other humans to understand
DrPacMan: @georgehotz what's your current laptop btw?
paradoxeryy: @hideoto more like the us, it's just that they're audacious enough to call out russians on something they're doing in the daily
ebashhustle1: кодзима гений
mexeroserisback: I think after 2 months working on this could be a nightmare
Number___Nine: commies are comming
mexeroserisback: logic makes you go insane
hanzo_93: LUL
jagger_rsw: Putin stronk
Number___Nine: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Russian Propaganda
grizvok: WASNT HE?
hideoto: Nah, not really. For example: Eventually the truth came out about WMD and the people who repeated it, admitted it
Quad___lol: @georgehotz who built pyramids :)
OmarBeBallin: @speeddrawing101 Jebaited
hideoto: Compare that to Russian stuff, they just keep lying no matter what
paradoxeryy: woah easy on the S word
Number___Nine: pyramidheads
mexeroserisback: I did :)
caslecasle: did i miss the asmr part today
twiggy_io: Pate life thankyou
caslecasle: F
speeddrawing101: @OmarBeBallin hamzOMEGALUL
Quad___lol: cmonBruh wait what
mexeroserisback: cmonBruh
paradoxeryy: ye we kid, we're kidders
Haffa: i remember when Britney was a slave for you
experimental_warrior: I've some slaves, on my database :P
xrealyy: Have you read Edward Snowden's book?
ebashhustle1: Can you pronounce "Kodzima geniy"?
SnakeOneMLG: there was an ASMR part with george eating ice
Caene: People still use slaves in the middle east and some parts of Africa, apparently. Like, slave trade and the whole thing.
averagesizepens: according to marx jobs are wage slavery,so we all slaves
OmarBeBallin: sumPirate xqcGob xqcGob2 m0xyEZ
Number___Nine: H1B visa slaves
prezk0: @georgehotz what does this has to do with AI? i'm a simpleton
prezk0: *have
paradoxeryy: @Number___Nine
jagger_rsw: but ifyou divide height of a pyramid in meters by length of its side in yards you'll get 666, an accident?
OmarBeBallin: real shit time monkaW
speeddrawing101: shroud1 shroud2 hamz7 hamz8
Haffa: well 1st wave slavery was ended by the industrial revolution, this 2nd wave will be ended by automation
whichtom: kanye was right dude
Daniel_Duan: It's various forms of control
0om4ar: ??
jagger_rsw: I'm a slav, and the word 'slave' comes from Latin 'sclave', which stands for slavs :), the more you know
minmaxy: what's the alternative?
caslecasle: "The best way to enslave somebody" xD
dawgwhisper007: ?
speeddrawing101: Geohot for president
mexeroserisback: Just like google convincing you that you can chose turn off location tracking Kappa
shlver: Is gehotz YangGang?
prezk0: ok, so can anyone in chat explain what he's coding has to do with AI?
averagesizepens: LUL
Quad___lol: KEKW
dawgwhisper007: Geohotz is not YangGang
OmarBeBallin: xqcP
paradoxeryy: @jagger_rsw actually false
experimental_warrior: what is that paper you're reading?
dawgwhisper007: 1000 give to me
Number___Nine: that dope sticker I VOTED though
raulciuntastefan: what do you think about Alex Jones ?
paradoxeryy: @jagger_rsw not goin explain just google the ethnonym
jagger_rsw: @paradoxeryy but wikipedia
Haffa: voting gives you right to complain tho :p
caslecasle: Schilling for Augur. Hope your getting paid for that
jagger_rsw: @paradoxeryy actually wiktionary
kilo_atl: Beto2020
OmarBeBallin: xqcT
minmaxy: cast protest votes then, they're counted too
OmarBeBallin: hmm xqcT
hideoto: Hotz 2030
jagger_rsw: @paradoxeryy 'From Middle English, from Old French sclave, from Medieval Latin sclāvus (“slave”), from Late Latin Sclāvus (“Slav”), because Slavs were often forced into slavery in the Middle Ages'
el_pirulote: @georgehotz more of this next stream will debate destiny
tunacan_man: Do you think automation will be impactful enough to cause serious economic issues, or will jobs just pop up in other sectors like they have every other time?
Number___Nine: 1m2019.com
cvbook: @geohot on the one-dimensional man great refusal
speeddrawing101: hamzL
dawgwhisper007: context = rock-> hammer or spear
mexeroserisback: well rounded fake news
kilo_atl: I just want the AI machine to be president
Daniel_Duan: i watch geohotz
grizvok: are you kidding yes
shlver: Automation already is lmao
Zacharycht: the odds of a better outcome are higher with voting then right?
whichtom: the question is when, not if
tunacan_man: The argument against that would be that more jobs were generated in other sectors
paradoxeryy: @jagger_rsw that's just the english derivation
paradoxeryy: @jagger_rsw ... itself a borrowing and Byzantine Greek σκλάβος sklábos "slave," which was in turn apparently derived from a misunderstanding of the Slavic autonym (denoting a speaker of their own languages).
Quad___lol: gender studies are the future
OmarBeBallin: you mean they developed machines that were able to replace the jobs a lot of humans did xqcT
Number___Nine: slaven sind sklaven
xrealyy: Fuck automation and AI
paradoxeryy: @jagger_rsw bla bla However, the origin of this word is disputed.
thomasmas: ?????????????
Keyeh: now look up services jobs over time
celiezz: 4th toilet run this stream?
Haffa: xrealyy ? why?
shlver: lol don't be a luddite.
iron_lasagna: !uptime
jagger_rsw: @paradoxeryy i don't like half winning the disputes ;)
Haffa: i would love to do nothing but what i wanted
zoki_macola: !uptime
grizvok: @tunacan_man some jobs will be generated in other sectors. that doesn't mean it's going to be some 1 to 1 thing
averagesizepens: wash hands pls
aresfour: i love these streams
sixd: is this a view of his whole house?
sixd: kitchen, bed
0om4ar: what the companies will be using all these people at ?
MrBankster: dude when will web dev no longer be a job?
dawgwhisper007: just learn rapidminer
Keyeh: now look up services jobs over times
Dawoud3: Hi George, could you explain how have you build the Comma.ai's device that controls the car (hardware, software), or do you want to keep it secret?
caslecasle: xD
paradoxeryy: @jagger_rsw idk why you're getting upset, it's just your average fail fun fact stuff
Xaotic: Somebody gift me a sub pls
OmarBeBallin: That graph should plot number of humans and machines working in water and maybe it would be consistent xqcT
Xaotic: I am in 3rd world country 5 usd is too much
grizvok: @MrBankster a LONG time.
Xaotic: gift me pl0x
jagger_rsw: @pai don't, just kidding, good to know more
Haffa: the guy handing out mints at the male toilets. we need those
Zacharycht: no'
Xaotic: I live in underdeveloped world @georgehotz
catacata92: The only thing that it is or can be bad it is stupidity, even if you are poor or an billionaire or 'slave' it does not matter if you do not have variations in thinking and you are close to an potato
jagger_rsw: @paradoxeryy i don't, just kidding, good to know more
Number___Nine: cooking stream
zgamer0123: George can u sum up all the things you have been doing, i've just arrived :D
paradoxeryy: @jagger_rsw
grizvok: @zgamer0123 its been a series of awesome tangents
friendfromfuture: Yeah can u sum up all the things you have been doing, i've just arrived
ProfElements1: Learning and failing of category theory
Lutefisk123: Yeah can u sum up all the things you have been doing, i've just arrived
dyslexicat: geohot stream FeelsGoodMan
dawgwhisper007: progamming jobs will be cut in half
prafaeltsantos: We don´t need jobs, every one is going to have heath and the machines do the job....... TheIlluminati TheIlluminati
Quad___lol: Yeah can u sum up all the things you have been doing, i am just retarded and stupid
jagger_rsw: cooking, I was thinking that geohot survives on pure python injected into veins
beginbot: They aren't just a doorman they are a door friends!
dawgwhisper007: hail rapidminer
Caene: You look healthy, George.
aresfour: @georgehotz are you tryna build the code search thing that erlang joe often talked about?
Number___Nine: healthy 2019
friendfromfuture: There was a talk about doorman
Number___Nine: like Putin
dyslexicat: PogChamp
dawgwhisper007: superficial
whichtom: why tho
Cal3b123: how come you have zotero installed 🤔
mexeroserisback: Kreygasm
Quad___lol: :D
JUST_5HEAD: lmfao
shlver: that's a goal? lmao why?
thomasmas: Kreygasm
jagger_rsw: just use some AI program to convert your pic
whichtom: aren't you a slave to instagram
Haffa: woowoo woo. TOS no guns on stream Kappa
xrealyy: can someone tell me why automation and AI is/will be good for us? Is it only to make life easier?
MrBankster: huge arms man
kito__: the question is are you eating enough
athmo2: dat biceps tho
Dawoud3: Hi George, could you explain how have you build the Comma.ai's device that controls the car (how did you connect hardware with software), or do you want to keep it secret?
hoffs: Do you have a day job rn george?
Keyeh: what do you think that with automation humans have been working more than ever in history?
Fulk33: did we prove true is not false yet?
dyslexicat: but true is false :)
aresfour: whats the endgame for humans tho
tornpaperyoyos: @dyslexicat lies
Number___Nine: "false" has more letters
dyslexicat: north korea LUL
swagettiyolonaise69: as if usa is a free country
Keyeh: free country KKona
c0alman: CarlSmile
shlver: It's a balancing act for the people in the power. Create inequality and work essential for survival, people become ignorant and only look forward to their biweekly payroll
directrix13: @georgehotz have you used ACL2?
Number___Nine: define "free"
dyslexicat: monkaS
tornpaperyoyos: china will ban you
hoffs: china big investor
Quad___lol: china is the best :)
averagesizepens: scared of china LUL
quickfloor: @georgehotz What's a day bro
MrBankster: get that china moneis
Number___Nine: no more Shengen trips
AntiVax_SoccerMom: MingLee "Yes cancel George Hotz right now"
xrealyy: Im wondering if Geo is better than Snowden in coding
ICAntF331MyFAce: That'll affect the bottom line
Keyeh: great country bro MingLee
mexeroserisback: monkaS
quickfloor: Also @georgehotz love's chines foods . like rice
raulciuntastefan: great country lulk
hideoto: Don't watch Winnie Pooh, ever again!
Xaotic: CHINA NUMBER 1
tornpaperyoyos: the new form of "dont taze me bro" LUL
astr0nils: china is going to be whats called world nowadays PogChamp and geohot is banned from the world
Quad___lol: @georgehotz just say HK is China and all good :)
sixd: what drugs are you on?
tornpaperyoyos: instead of "dont taze me bro" nowadays its "dont cancel me bro" LUL
okeeeeeee: george hotz stream PogChamp
quickfloor: !uptime
c0alman: @sixd Caffeine :)
MrBankster: how much adderral you do this morning?
paradoxeryy: @xrealyy how do they even compare lol, snowden is known for his activism while george is for his dev stuff, you just picked two famous techies
Keyeh: i'm 21 :)
FargioFarmani: @georgehotz What is your opinion about Siraj Raval?
quickfloor: @FargioFarmani is he on drugs ?
dorkmo: a/s/l ?
okeeeeeee: LUL
MatiGoG: ^
W1lkins: how are the airpod pros Kappa
shlver: idk man, once i quit weed my productivity shot through the roof
MatiGoG: exposed
dannyy_r: so do you guys think the growing amount of programming jobs is just a bubble that is gonna burst in the future and then there aren't going to be a lot of jobs in the future and lots of cs dudes with no job
Keyeh: monkaS
Quad___lol: what about sir raj?
paradoxeryy: @W1lkins works for Palantir, say what
okeeeeeee: wastes 280$ LUL
SnakeOneMLG: you mentioned them on last stream
lemonboxed: leaf juice is potent drug
dorkmo: subaru video
W1lkins: it was mentioned on the company who shall not be named stream
slArkBig: are you going to buy the latest 16 inch mbp
dannyy_r: OH NO
prafaeltsantos: what...adderall helps concentration???
hoffs: coke laced green leaf tea
spitza: Can you code while on weed?
Keyeh: dude the proof that true is not false is RIGHT THERE
quickfloor: !uptime
friendfromfuture: if there is no jobs then how will people be able to buy food?
paradoxeryy: @prafaeltsantos ye, it adds more erall's to your system
quickfloor: why uptime doesn't work ?
murkythunder: TRUE
Cal3b123: @keyeh lol
MrBankster: sometime you should do a stream where you hack video games
mexeroserisback: ex falso quodlibet
Number___Nine: spitza yes, but you gonna need a lot of adderall to fix that afterwards
lemonboxed: that means u r learning
Vjasal: false -> true = true
Number___Nine: ANON_6
dimplik: is this prolog?
eax_ebx: coq
swsh: you can prove anythong from false, that's what false is
okeeeeeee: ??????
Number___Nine: some serious formal prove shite
murkythunder: prove that you can it 4Head
Fulk33: prove it by contradiction
quickfloor: Like false isn't true but true is false ? NotLikeThis
mexeroserisback: True and not True -> False
Number___Nine: so... we can't after all lmao
swsh: Coq is garbage
asaalgk: it gets taught in the first class of discrete math
sk84uhlivin: sk84uhlivin subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Keyeh: bruh contradiction in 2019
mexeroserisback: Cant you just assume True and not True and then leave out the not True to prove True
Cal3b123: https://math.stackexchange.com/a/1583244
dimplik: George Hotz the 1st, brought to his knees by the scripture written on half a pdf page.
sk84uhlivin: Glad you brought the coq files back, have fun :)
shlver: whats happening? OpieOP
Fulk33: whats H?
tornpaperyoyos: what language is George programming in
sk84uhlivin: Coq
Keyeh: god's language
Number___Nine: assert(true == false)
movAX13h: true can not exist w/o false
gimmighyone: you are speaking the language of gods
jbyte1988: good jon
jbyte1988: good job
gimmighyone: good john
astr0nils: good joe
jbyte1988: StoneLightning
Fulk33: love how @georgehotz is just guessing the next step and pretends he understands when its right :DDD
Number___Nine: hack the logic
okeeeeeee: ^ lol
swsh: False is an empty set, the proof is just no definition by Curry-Horward
Keyeh: he's doing a random search bro
ornis1: Что он делает?
hoffs: is anything ever true
gimmighyone: @Fulk33 fake it till you make it
tornpaperyoyos: @ornis1 hes trying to prove true is not false
itsChoudhry: I just tuned in what is this? what's the paper?
tornpaperyoyos: should change the stream message to "can we prove that false implies true"
volere: does george have a twitter
JUST_5HEAD: now im hungry too fuck
Unsavable: What is the actuation force for these switches?
okeeeeeee: tendies burger?
Quad___lol: proving something is not is easier than something is :)
MrBankster: microwave don't take 25 mins
Unsavable: They sound so heavy
tornpaperyoyos: should change the stream message to "can we prove that false implies true"
luxbock: @georgehotz note that the arrow in the book does not mean "implies", it is more general and implication can be one form that it takes in a suitable setting, but if you read it as implies everytime you will be confused later
Caene: @georgehotz You clearly excel in what you're doing, programming and whatnot. Why do you think that is? What brought you to that point? Just lucked out on genes and turned out "smart" straight out the vagina? Or would you say there's a specific thing, that other people can somewhat mimic/train themselves to do? Do you do something specific? Visualize problems/solutions in your head? Anything special?
JUST_5HEAD: imagine not visualizing LUL
d0ubletruth: @Caene its called adderall
Number___Nine: ornis1 формально доказывает что true != false
zoki_macola: rust is better than python
Mariosavitch: what the hell are these blog posts
tornpaperyoyos: should change the stream message to "can we prove that false implies true"
superragetastic: this is a family friendly stream boys and girls Kappa
bytebacon: Category theory is plenty useful in functional programming
Keyeh: some joe rogan dmt shit right there
samtheprogram: Find a rust zero-day
Mariosavitch: ???
swsh: category theory can make you feel smart Kappa
camrod91: @Extern
AntiVax_SoccerMom: LUL
UrWifeMyKids: LUL
AntiVax_SoccerMom: DO IT PogChamp
Mariosavitch: false implies true my friend @georgehotz
MonkaSupreme: diy stream PogChamp
ornis1: @Number___Nine А для чего? Он пытается сделать свой ЯП?
okeeeeeee: confirmed PogChamp
Quad___lol: POG
Keyeh: do it and stream it PogChamp
gazny: Test it to prove it wrong
Quad___lol: DO IT
volere: seems this is your next project
grizvok: LOL
JUST_5HEAD: LMFAOO
MonkaSupreme: DO IT PogChamp
MonkaSupreme: donation goal PogChamp
JUST_5HEAD: XAAXAXAXAXAX
ziyaedin: I just ordered one
Keyeh: infrared bro
Number___Nine: ornis1 учиться как доказывать на языке coq
hkisthebest: @georgehotz where do you live?
W1lkins: This is prime hn shit
MonkaSupreme: XAXA?
okeeeeeee: fake graphs LUL
asaalgk: OMEGALUL
Keyeh: LUL
MonkaSupreme: lol
Quad___lol: LULW
Mariosavitch: is that cummulative searches?
bytebacon: Make slam in Haskell
UrWifeMyKids: LUL
okeeeeeee: its only usa, the world is caring about it Kappa @georgehotz
JUST_5HEAD: LOOOL
tornpaperyoyos: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
soisoisoi: LUL
grizvok: TENDIES
lemonboxed: one of our worm ancestors evolved by being able to detect light with a hole in its head
grizvok: TENDIES ALARM
Number___Nine: food is here
movAX13h: easier to put everything in a box for machines to learn
Quad___lol: porn
Mariosavitch: debt
AntiVax_SoccerMom: gold
AntiVax_SoccerMom: silver
MonkaSupreme: gold
Quad___lol: search for porn
Cal3b123: pretty sure graph in blog is ngram graph
hkisthebest: search geohotz
ragemaster999: what papers are you reading?
dorkmo: whats in the oven?
asaalgk: based
dorkmo: it beeped!
Hueston94: Besides Zotero Connector and uBlock Origin what is the other extension you use?
dorkmo: is it done?
superragetastic: tendiiiieees SwiftRage
Fulk33: Dude I bet mathematicians like math so much because LaTeX makes it look so good that yiu wanna bust a nut
W1lkins: dorkmo, no he just put it in and it takes 45 min
gazny: This just looks like Inequality squares
dorkmo: aw cool
okeeeeeee: tendies panicBasket
AntiVax_SoccerMom: so why is category theory so cool now?
lemonboxed: you can save on tender refrigeration cost by shipping live chicken
bytebacon: Jordan Peterson hates postmodernists
Cal3b123: so when are you ordering the near infared lamp
whichtom: all the more reason to trust them
W1lkins: Nice review "dont waste you're time" Kappa
Quad___lol: :D
lemonboxed: maybe its working for him
Number___Nine: AntiVax_SoccerMom because of all the bugs in software people are trying to switch to "safe" more abstract languages
samtheprogram: Predict the next recession based on the popularity of category theory
superragetastic: jp doesn't know what postmodernism means :(
Quad___lol: DO IT
Quad___lol: buy a huge infrared lamp
W1lkins: can you prove that a chicken can be turned into tenders using coq
samtheprogram: That’s like regular business development
tornpaperyoyos: should change the stream title to "can we prove that false implies true"
bytebacon: Postmodernists are a bunch of verysmarts
W1lkins: yo bro, what wavelength of infra-red light are you using these days
Mariosavitch: the term "unemployment" would be better
Fulk33: Lets write a turing machine, that can write to its transition function
revolutionist123: i do it always, what the problem? 🤔
Number___Nine: clear correlation
AntiVax_SoccerMom: Number___Nine ah ty
grizvok: LOL
whichtom: based on a sample size of 1
dorkmo: leading indicator!
Number___Nine: bored mathematicians lost jobs as business analysts
scatterp2: correlation does not imply causation
yum72: add bitcoin
averagesizepens: is he trolling, i might belive that
Keyeh: fake economy KKona
AntiVax_SoccerMom: thats teh pump
pereyy: i really hope you are trolling right now
alphasweetpea: Im just tuning in, now i gotta google category theory
Number___Nine: Nakamoto
superragetastic: Galaxy fuckin brain PogChamp
xLequix: is this still twitch?
JUST_5HEAD: Kappa
pereyy: google trends are not leading indicators of anything dude
okeeeeeee: do a ted talk about it @georgehotz
bytebacon: @scatterp2 models don't necessarily need to differentiate that for them to be useful.
JUST_5HEAD: and infrared
averagesizepens: LUL
jagger_rsw: corellation not causation? :)
wiseai: 5Head
pereyy: large funds know whats happening before the public
alphasweetpea: Bitcoin has artifical supply, which is a red flag for me
Jimbo51: ig nobel prize coming your way
grizvok: at least a tedx talk
pereyy: to suggest otherwise is complete nonsense
MonkaSupreme: your paper is gonna influence the google trends results for category theory, so you have to adjust for that Kappa
JUST_5HEAD: noise?
W1lkins: throw some infra-red light in there too somewhere
revolutionist123: PogChamp i just gain 1 more iq
okeeeeeee: holy its true PogChamp
no742617000027: is this real life? first time i catch a live stream Kreygasm
MonkaSupreme: right now you are pumping category theory trends LUL
Number___Nine: haskell mafia
Keyeh: you so smart dude, have you been shining infrared light this morning?
wiseai: Kappa
revolutionist123: @georgehotz check if is white noise
alphasweetpea: Hey is there any movement on your maps solution
lemonboxed: whats the difference between infrared light and chemical x
bytebacon: Can you verify that with a couple of more companies? Microsoft? Amazon?
751469823: alpha for sure
Ammar410: hello
murkythunder: LUL
Keyeh: LUL
camrod91: Are we still in a simulation?
samtheprogram: This is amazing
naabee_: Goodhart's Law
Zabiak12345: PogChamp
christian__james: that's a reverse 5Head
Number___Nine: is category theory scam?
JUST_5HEAD: your food is ready
W1lkins: delete the vod @georgehotz
alphasweetpea: Thats smart
wiseai: we are not going to tell no one
revolutionist123: too complex for me, can you go back to companies roasts? @georgehotz
Ammar410: do u know abt RPA Development?
dorkmo: subscriber only vod for catagory theory wisdom
MonkaSupreme: buy buy 📈
christian__james: I agree
lemonboxed: you can use category theory to destroy goodharts law
murkythunder: suscribe to onlyfans
SKPTCL: sec alert
unikid93: KNOCK KNOCK SEC
grizvok: im down
samtheprogram: I always ruin stuff by observing it
alphasweetpea: Lol i hope SEC isnt here
SKPTCL: ive been undercover
Sullyboy: isnt that illegal lol
murkythunder: funds r safu
AntiVax_SoccerMom: monkaS
PanicPoint: I’m in
MonkaSupreme: lets do it 📈
alphasweetpea: Thats only allowed by wallstreet banks George
Vjasal: selling penny stocks big? i think i saw that in a movie
dyslexicat: monkaS
soopu: h
revolutionist123: the next wolf?
adriaroms: macOS?
superragetastic: studio apartment costs 4k
revolutionist123: cooking steam? PogChamp
W1lkins: it hasn't been 45 min, he's gonna be poisoned :)
W1lkins: RIP boys
jagger_rsw: even people programming in coq must eat
superragetastic: incoming salmonella :(
raulciuntastefan: lol
Number___Nine: coq people only eat prana
adriaroms: Yep
JUST_5HEAD: CHEW LOUDER 😡
abita: social eating
adriaroms: adriaroms subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 3 months, currently on a 2 month streak! hello
superragetastic: MUKBANG
jagger_rsw: isn't it in coq community guidelines that all coq porgrammers should eat only kale
bytebacon: ASMR
revolutionist123: chewing noise DansGame
Extrn: eta wen
h4ns_b4mbel: Metamath zero > Coq
Fulk33: @georgehotz I like to think the universe is a probabilistic cellular automata with a cell size close to the plank length, thoughts?
bytebacon: Where can I buy the label-less keyboard that George uses?
lemonboxed: every stream becomes asmr
lemonboxed: at some point
SimStig: what are we coding?
superragetastic: AGI
movAX13h: @Fulk33 Nikola Tesla said that atomism is nonsense
scatterp2: @luxbock do you know how to apply category theory in practice ?
bytebacon: George, checkout Mendeley. Makes it super easy to manage all your papers
lemonboxed: this sounds like the edm version of elevator music
swsh: Let's learn Lean Theorem Prover
volere: PepePls
anthraxvirus322: what are we coding today chat :)
okeeeeeee: templeos in recommendations LUL
camrod91: lol templeos
Keyeh: RIP terry
anthraxvirus322: neural network PogChamp
anthraxvirus322: POG
oksan309: RIP grandpa kitchen
gazny: Temple os Recommended PogChamp
lemonboxed: looks like worldcat.org
anthraxvirus322: monkaS
AntiVax_SoccerMom: shame
anthraxvirus322: what was that
bytebacon: Complicated Hilbert Spaces
Keyeh: he was trying to prove that thix axiom was true
pkacprzak: @bytebacon that'll be remembered for many years
C4TFive: We about to solve fermat's last theorem live on twitch
revolutionist123: here comes the time we realise how stupid we are
superragetastic: tendies are done
lemonboxed: it was implied
anthraxvirus322: LUL tendies done SeemsGood
swsh: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dp-mQ3HxgDE Dude says they're close at formalising Ferma in Lean
anthraxvirus322: NotLikeThis
Keyeh: almost Kappa
anthraxvirus322: almos Kapp
h4ns_b4mbel: Mindfuck O.o
superragetastic: we want tendies
anthraxvirus322: talking about chat monkaS
averagesizepens: wash hands pls
anthraxvirus322: wash hands DansGame
lemonboxed: has anyone tried brushing oil on the outside of tendies and airfrying
revolutionist123: never wash hands LUL
xrealyy: where
C4TFive: Unwashed bathroom hands give the tendies that je ne sais quoi
okeeeeeee: Kreygasm
anthraxvirus322: Kreygasm
anthraxvirus322: what logic is this FeelsWeirdMan
lemonboxed: a little fecal matter improves your immune system
FargioFarmani: Very good reason indeed
okeeeeeee: "germs cant fly high"
bytebacon: wash hands vs. use sanitizer
revolutionist123: sure Kappa
unikid93: what if the line that intersects the first triangle edge is parallel to on of the other sides of the triangle @georgehotz
wiseai: PowerPoint time
anthraxvirus322: powerpoint ResidentSleeper
lemonboxed: isn't it like 1000 pages of proofs
bytebacon: newton was one hell of a mathboi
lemonboxed: mathlad*
anthraxvirus322: is this used in moden algos ?
bytebacon: absolute mathlad
FargioFarmani: What if eating raw chicken would improve your gut flora? @georgehotz
lemonboxed: unit
zoki_macola: those windows are messing with my ocd
awesomeo113: Ayyy
Number___Nine: twitchmath
Mariosavitch: we did it
JUST_5HEAD: metameth lkmao
lemonboxed: metameth
W1lkins: twitch meth
Mariosavitch: we are already on metameth
awesomeo113: I love meth
awesomeo113: I mean math
lemonboxed: metameth is infra-red coke beamed straight into your dome
lemonboxed: nostrils
god_damn: the reddit classic
anthraxvirus322: @awesomeo113 open up monkaS
speejay1: george I type faster than you bro
JUST_5HEAD: what if they think infrared in your brain is cool ? :)
mcdrizzle_: I always outsource my thinking to top reddit comments
Number___Nine: they've scammed geo into a meme
Quad___lol: but we are sourcing our thinking to you so make a good decision
CaptCalifornia: CaptCalifornia subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 3 months, currently on a 3 month streak! i work at Amazon and it fucking blows can you please do more leetcode on stream so i can pass my Google interview in January? big thanks bro
revolutionist123: licking unwashed hands Kreygasm
CaptCalifornia: man FUCK u
BootsForCats: opening this many tabs gives me anxiety
Quad___lol: only idiots work for corporations
Number___Nine: found your own company
CaptCalifornia: nah nah im not trolling lol
CaptCalifornia: I mean I was trying to be funny but I'm serious
CaptCalifornia: cmonBruh
CaptCalifornia: any team, they all get free food
grizvok: really deep
bytebacon: georgieboi - he slacc, he hacc, but most importantly he loves his snacc
anthraxvirus322: what do you think of AWS @CaptCalifornia is it as bad as amazon ?
Number___Nine: no free food at amazon?
JUST_5HEAD: @CaptCalifornia thats the thing
bulbaz0r: george how do you get a data science job that isn't shit is the real question
CaptCalifornia: NO WTF
god_damn: bro amazon doesnt have free bathrooms
CaptCalifornia: @anthraxvirus322 yeah i'm on AWS
JUST_5HEAD: lmao
minmaxy: yep, amazonian here too
FargioFarmani: Amazon is not a great place to work at, I heard
revolutionist123: LUL
CaptCalifornia: LMAO
W1lkins: I wanna work on the hangouts team
lemonboxed: amazon buys wholefoods does not have free food
W1lkins: oh wait Kappa
Mariosavitch: they dont even have gender bathrooms
anon543264: lmao
Number___Nine: amazon warehose
SnakeOneMLG: facebook best company probably
anthraxvirus322: @CaptCalifornia damn i was preparing for AWS
wiseai: NO FOOD OMEGALUL
Free3ze: OpieOP
CaptCalifornia: I literally go to whole foods 3 times a day and give my money BACK TO JEFF BEZOS FUCK
revolutionist123: probably pay to work LUL
grizvok: shit i have free snacks at my company and we're worth only 400mil
Attlantiz_: a
pkacprzak: that's awesome, imagine people picking jobs like 100 years ago based on free food perks
minmaxy: yeah it's the "frugality" principle
th3_maj0r: Does "the company that we can't talk about" offer free food?
anthraxvirus322: @CaptCalifornia which division are u working in i mean service ?
Quad___lol: google propaganda, results have been adjusted
W1lkins: that's a yes th3_maj0r
Number___Nine: is food free at backspace.ai?
CaptCalifornia: @anthraxvirus322 O
CaptCalifornia: @anthraxvirus322 I'm on an AWS EC2 team
bytebacon: i work for HERE. making autonomous car shizz
ibimsmarry: how is comma getting revenue?
unikid93: Hi amazonians pls teach us how to use lambda
th3_maj0r: A disgusted "yes"
CaptCalifornia: @georgehotz aight putting in my application now LUL
jagger_rsw: working project-zero is not bad, on the left best haxor in the world, on the right second best haxoor, your manager is a really good haxxor
leknar: does comma.ai offer free food ?
littlebighead82: is this an asmr channel ?!?!
stalys_: imagine going outside in 2019
CaptCalifornia: LOOOOOOOOOOL thank you
cybergenik: George I'm about to graduate school can I apply to your company, maybe just as a Jr. Dev or something.
okeeeeeee: LUL
anthraxvirus322: LUL
wiseai: A M A Z OMEGALUL N
W1lkins: leknar banned
awesomeo113: I’d prefer to not work for a company that says implements bias
FargioFarmani: Now all I have to do is to pass the Google Interview...
cybergenik: pleeaaaaaaaaase
Number___Nine: free bar at comma
jagger_rsw: is it easier to get hired at project-zero or at comma? :)
caslecasle: jesus
tris790: hahaha
zenkai_oogway: DansGame
Ya_mums_granny: DansGame
god_damn: run it under the tap
Quad___lol: suck it
gordovolador: DansGame
pereyy: tendies in the keys NotLikeThis
Fight_Stick: clean it with a toothbrush
xrealyy: how many employees do you have in comma
tunacan_man: @god_damn LUL
bytebacon: @captcalifornia what is "bursting" exactly when it comes to t2/t3 instances?
Julean: wait he doesnt have symbols on his keyboard
minmaxy: that's the thing, working at Amazon is my way of proving that I pass the bar, maybe not comma's though
CaptCalifornia: @bytebacon I have no fucking idea dawg
Number___Nine: lear how to coq
lemonboxed: leave the tender inside as a reward
Number___Nine: *learn
okeeeeeee: "bar at comma is very high, i have chicken tenders in my keyboard"
AntiVax_SoccerMom: classy
FargioFarmani: lol microwaving food?
CaptCalifornia: I did 30 minutes of work for Amazon this entire last week I just went to other floors and leetcoded at work all day
yum72: https://i.imgur.com/9JQzKOn.gifv
kiedy_sweter: @georgehotz what is your opinion about self d... estructive animals like giant pacific octopuses?
CaptCalifornia: LUL understood
wiseai: LEARN HOW TO COOK AND CODE
W1lkins: I've learned how to remove chicken tendies from my keyboard
bytebacon: free personal nvidia DGX-2 for new comma employees
W1lkins: and to point near infra-red light at my head
Number___Nine: cook and coq
awesomeo113: He protec, he attac, but most importantly, he ban your acc
eax_ebx: learn how to chill.
Quad___lol: does comma ai offer free hookers and wild parties?
W1lkins: Quad___lol banned
Number___Nine: Quad___lol no, but you get to watch geo's streams IRL
CaptCalifornia: @Quad___lol nah that's uber
Attlantiz_: they have strippers
unikid93: @Quad___lol yea they do and everyone can get drunk because the ai drives them hookers back
K0enich: i heard Stratton Oakmont offers these services for their employees
CaptCalifornia: KEKW
Mariosavitch: jordan belfort hedge fund
CaptCalifornia: BOOMER D:
Attlantiz_: what happened to the razer laptop george
wiseai: BOOMER
god_damn: he really abou tit
Mariosavitch: you said you like ponzi schemes
xrealyy: where's razer laptop
okeeeeeee: cmonBruh
Number___Nine: Attlantiz_ he's selling it
lemonboxed: snitches get movie deals
Attlantiz_: did you not like it xD»
xrealyy: no minecraft anymore?
Attlantiz_: the Dell XPS 15 looks pretty nice
cybergenik: Wait why did you sell ti what happened/
Mariosavitch: logic is a transparent ponzi scheme
Attlantiz_: or a thinkpad
bytebacon: you mean complicated numbers?
Number___Nine: Attlantiz_ or Lenovo X1 Extreme Gen2
Attlantiz_: yeah thats a thinkpad
Number___Nine: Attlantiz_ I hear cooling is better in Lenovo
wiseai: Louis Rossmann told me only to buy thinkpads :)
xxxelent: lol
SKPTCL: stream rename: metamath phase 1
Attlantiz_: thinkpad is lenovo @Number___Nine
lemonboxed: documentation looks reasonable
jaalle: Damn are we done with cock
nahamsec: 72 raiders from nahamsec have joined!
b1tc0d3: its a raid boiis
minmaxy: at least all the tangent talking serves a purpose
euranymous: RAIDDDDDD
Attlantiz_: no more co(ck) for george
740ii: nahamsDupsman
Ekaeo: raid
euranymous: nahamsBountyplz
r4416: so are you gonna migrate everything to metamath?
Number___Nine: Terry Davis HolyC.mp4
r4416: your previous code?
Attlantiz_: george have you looked at the thinkpads x1
b1tc0d3: ooh basic math Kappa
euranymous: We need @georgehotz as a guest in @nahamsec 's stream
W1lkins: Grothendieck Kreygasm
Number___Nine: Attlantiz_ after using Razor he called win10 the boomer shite, so I suppose he's not interested
Ash_F0x: Let's go @nahamsec raid!
awesomeo113: I hate it at google. I’m interviewing to go work at WeWork. Wish me luck @georgehotz
CaptCalifornia: @awesomeo113 what the fuck
Attlantiz_: boooomeeeer. A linux dist would be pretty nice too or even a hackintosh
whichtom: holy shit nahamsec damn
xxxelent: @awesomeo113 idk what wework is but pog
Attlantiz_: he seemed to like windows 10 a lot in the first days though xD
Number___Nine: Attlantiz_ linux doesn't even have the floppy driver
euranymous: LUL
Attlantiz_: do you need floppy drivers lmao
minmaxy: just install it and find out how it works
Attlantiz_: is that for floppy disks
slow_manatee: link it
CaptCalifornia: EZ
euranymous: link
alphasweetpea: I learned application of math before I learned the theory
Number___Nine: math hackers work at NSA
minmaxy: http://us.metamath.org/#downloads
CaptCalifornia: @alphasweetpea I never truly learned either FeelsBadMan
Attlantiz_: methmath
EugeneIonesco: WeWork is the latest IPO hotness
Attlantiz_: why is everyone doing IPOs lmao
neptun44: what's up boys
anon543264: @georgehotz did you graduate from university?
neptun44: whats happening
CaptCalifornia: Pog @neptun44 here's
Attlantiz_: they all want to suck on the money tit
CaptCalifornia: is here*
bytebacon: Check this out: https://theoremprover-museum.github.io/
Number___Nine: that's what businesses do
Attlantiz_: @anon543264 HE dropped from carnegie mellon afaik
xxxelent: this pdf is existentially moving
Number___Nine: twitchread
SKPTCL: :/
Attlantiz_: nooooo georgeee dont leave us
okeeeeeee: BibleThump
SnakeOneMLG: link it
SKPTCL: read it
anon543264: @Attlantiz_ thanks
okeeeeeee: link?
SKPTCL: with stream onm
wiseai: link pdf
CaptCalifornia: pce out enjoy ✌️
Attlantiz_: yesssss
wiseai: link the pdf
SKPTCL: comfy
Ash_F0x: can you link the pdf plz?
purplepinapples: http://us.metamath.org/downloads/metamath.pdf
SnakeOneMLG: yes read it with the stream on
Ash_F0x: thanks
SKPTCL: reading with geohot :D
Keyeh: WeSmart stream
Attlantiz_: what is the pdf aboyt
Number___Nine: does geo read as fast as he types?
jay_al97: read together
Number___Nine: reading book ASMR
Attlantiz_: george do you suggest any books for like math and stuff for pre uni? or maybe for compsci
Number___Nine: geo read aloud, plz
naabee_: @georgehotz https://imo-grand-challenge.github.io/
Number___Nine: nvm, I am trolling
Number___Nine: siri can read though
meedofenom: what are we doing here guys ?
Number___Nine: meedofenom reading a book
iTeQo_: Next page pls
meedofenom: i mean .. the title ... true is not false ?
Number___Nine: meedofenom formally prove that
Attlantiz_: not(False) = True Kappa
lidermaury: come back later when you done reading
Number___Nine: how many pages left?
systemd_is_skynet: hopefully a lot
meedofenom: oh, ok ... proof by contradiction ?
Attlantiz_: induction
W1lkins: Number___Nine look at the scroll bar bruh
kanogger: reading stream
meridiansis: Terry Davis in the recommended section
Number___Nine: meedofenom prove by SAT solving
meridiansis: :(
Attlantiz_: george do you have a kindle or something like that for ebooks
Attlantiz_: or pdfs
meedofenom: i miss this things from school :)
dontbeameme: Quantum computing ?
swsh: Thoughts? https://reference.wolfram.com/language/ref/FindEquationalProof.html
Number___Nine: Of course, you still don't understand how...
Number___Nine: true
School47: Quantum is The rock
Attlantiz_: quantum is a buzz word Kappa
Number___Nine: quantum supremacy
Attlantiz_: the media come up with all of the bs to get attention
dontbeameme: Quantum programming
meedofenom: what is this book ?
alphasweetpea: Still fun to listen to in a group setting
AntiVax_SoccerMom: ima take a deuce and get some pizza, cya guys
Attlantiz_: @meedofenom http://us.metamath.org/downloads/metamath.pdf
W1lkins: PDF is laying out George's future
MonkaSupreme: its german lol
meedofenom: @Attlantiz_ thx
Number___Nine: you stream reading a book and getting money from twitch
Number___Nine: what a time to me alive
Number___Nine: *be
meedofenom: still better than just dance
renatobarresi: NotLikeThis
dontbeameme: We in simulation nothing is true
systemd_is_skynet: i cant watch if he's not clicking randomly
zigzati: @dontbeameme no
swsh: is there any colab pdf reading app?
W1lkins: swsh would you really wanna collab with twitch chat
Number___Nine: talk is cheap show me the code
swsh: true NotLikeThis
tris790: norman mcgill
vvapi: I wonder if stuff like this combined with fuzzing or neural nets could be useful
Number___Nine: just train AI to do math for you
minmaxy: that's him, says it in the linkedin review
movAX13h: @Number___Nine thats one reason this topic is so popular
dontbeameme: Use touchscreen it’s 2019 and you still clicking
0om4ar: BabyRage @number___nine
grizvok: why would he use a touchscreen
movAX13h: @Number___Nine math has to be formalized for AI to work on maths stuff
W1lkins: This guy is an NSA contractor Kappa
W1lkins: "Boston information group" sure Kappa
FurikuriYugi: I got a touchscreen laptop and it was so cool but then back to ext mouse cause real life work lol
W1lkins: add him on linkedin
jagger_rsw: fyi Google CTF is in progress, I see some cool challsin the sandbox category :)
shieeeeeeeeet: have you ever tried using Firefox tree style tabs?
jagger_rsw: https://gctf-2019.appspot.com/#challenges/
Number___Nine: $31337
minmaxy: says June
sebiyy: true is not false because my mama said so
yab_kat: is it just me or is your connection a bit slower today?
sebiyy: is your head big ? or is it the camera angle
jagger_rsw: macosx, one needs root passwd to read a *.c file :)
dontbeameme: Show pw
Number___Nine: lol
School47: LUL
Number___Nine: read the book, not the chat
4play_: what mouse do you use? sounds clickety clickey
minmaxy: at this point we're on level 15 of the tangent anyway
MonkaSupreme: LUL
HousedHorse: Steve J OMEGALUL bs
swsh: code your own MetaMath verifier, that would nice
dontbeameme: Take a shot
fkham: holy, its the one and only! whats up george!
dontbeameme: True is only true because the simulation says so
systemd_is_skynet: huh
Number___Nine: sounds like those guys at AI LAB MAC HACK and AI Memos
asaalgk: someones been following wildberger
Number___Nine: research grants?
dontbeameme: No money = not cool
zigzati: wtf is a computer
TCarriesYou: Hi I love ur content, i'm a broke student but once I get some cash i'll be subbing to "your shit"!
zigzati: im watching from ipad
FurikuriYugi: Money == tool
dontbeameme: No money = no vagina
exclamationpointe: wanna take over the world w me
hoffs: keep those people out of my gates
dontbeameme: Posers make good memes
Number___Nine: homebrew selfdriving cars
iskjmss: fucking hack my dna
ProfessorMagikarp0: clip it Kappa
milanx64: Yeah I agree....too much money.....its not even fair fruit of labour....
slow_manatee: turn it into a pyramid scheme
revolutionist123: so we watching porn now or what?
exclamationpointe: y is thag necessary the internet is here just git gud
milanx64: Like Arnold Schwarz did the true american dream and he has 400 mil net and yet Jeff Bezos worked the same amount or less and had 210 billion
meridiansis: are there any pictures?
sebiyy: i want to be your e-girlfriend
alphasweetpea: Lower than i would think
3even: So does Larry David
MonkaSupreme: LUL
ekalsuwaidi: cmonBruh
my_curiosity: :D
hoffs: cmonBruh
dontbeameme: Kanye made 5$ dad shoes 300$
vave2_: cmonBruh
exclamationpointe: lol spongebob meme “thirty years later” i bet after i _______ ill understand what catehroh therory is
orami: cmonBruh
sebiyy: he used all on steroids
sebiyy: Kapp
robbsalm: @georgehotz how to pass linear algebra?
AntiVax_SoccerMom: wasnt he a millionaire before he started his acting career? selling exercise equipment or something
ProfessorMagikarp0: need eye tracker so we can follow along with reading Kappa
grizvok: dude was a millionaire from selling supplements long before he was like super wealthy from body building i think
orami: Austria PogChamp
Number___Nine: got get distracted bro
grizvok: he hustled
movAX13h: it is STyria
milanx64: Imagine if we put like a 10 bil or so upper cap on wealth then used it for the environment ...ah now im too political
movAX13h: part of Austria in Central Europe
W1lkins: Jebaited
grizvok: YES
3even: HAHAHAHAHA
Number___Nine: environment is a scam
sebiyy: Kappa
CondomsWontFit: yes please
Ya_mums_granny: DO IT
orami: 🔨 BAN
whichtom: LUL
iskjmss: B A N
sterowiecp: LUL
grizvok: BAN
hoffs: communism is the solution
grizvok: END HIM
3even: "HoW dARe YoU!"
dontbeameme: Yes
sebiyy: JUST make a cap and give the rest to me
valleyisle: jokerd6Gold
dontbeameme: 100%
Number___Nine: dollar bills are green just as grass and trees
jagger_rsw: out of cotton i think
st47ik: bitcoin can be in paper too Kappa
W1lkins: how many trees did you save @georgehotz I saw Elon saved 1M trees Kappa
iskjmss: @Number___Nine duuuude weed is green too
zoki_macola: cannibalism
sebiyy: 420IQ
FurikuriYugi: Chickens will eat chicken
milanx64: lo
Caene: poor guy :(
milanx64: lol
FurikuriYugi: True story
hoffs: well 10 bil wont be dollar bills it will be couple of bits
Sublimus7: chickens will happily eat chickens
hkisthebest: @georgehotz how much is your net worth, I can't find it online
orami: XD
FargioFarmani: but money is not solely paper
robbsalm: how do I pass math courses in computer science? damn professors kinda sucks
FurikuriYugi: Nun Ya
dontbeameme: Never mind the cargo ships
LinhoArecon: 4 mill i think
jagger_rsw: monies are not paper, used to be cotton, nowplastic etc.
valleyisle: jokerd6Gold tree hugger
3even: USA USA USA
sebiyy: buy a 9 mil like h3h3
sebiyy: 9mil house
dontbeameme: All land will be New York City
SKPTCL: what city would you buy land in?
dawgwhisper007: military
pereman2: can u reverse a list ? BabyRage
estilen: bruh
dontbeameme: yep
robbsalm: can you reverse a linked list?
sebiyy: light is flickering
dontbeameme: They pick and choose
whichtom: the illusion of freedom
st47ik: how about privacy in the US?
valleyisle: Same KKona 🇺🇸
movAX13h: every country has a constitution
prafaeltsantos: bro.....Portugal....come here.....
whichtom: the collective koolaid
Caene: and yet the words on the document means nothing, since it's not being applied
W1lkins: yeah because it's always adhered to Kappa
dorkmo: "read my new white paper, the constituton of the united states of american"
hoffs: yeah like p much every other country has constitution
dawgwhisper007: you were a slave owner
valleyisle: America is just better emoneyKona
Fight_Stick: much better than relationship and money under the table states "shitholes" we people live in
sebiyy: MA GUNS
mystkomir: is it hard to get yourself to work? @georgehotz
jagger_rsw: Pharaoh's egypt lasted like 5k of years
quickfloor: That is hard cuz you didn't made for it @georgehotz . you made to be an engineer
Sublimus7: America is one of the only cultures where it was formally defined by smart people at the outset
Number___Nine: Founding Fathers hacked rights
SKPTCL: what state would you buy a house in?
Sublimus7: Not perfect, but a start
valleyisle: xqcG 2nd amendment
Caene: how is constitutional monarchy not based on principal?
dontbeameme: USA USA USA
dawgwhisper007: SLAVE OWNER
quickfloor: China ? :D
Number___Nine: just wait for the Mars Colony
hoffs: founding fathers is such a meme name
movAX13h: england, netherlands
jagger_rsw: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Constitution_of_3_May_1791
movAX13h: today
quickfloor: So you like trump :D
Richardable: Have you watched the Zuckerberg hearings? @georgehotz
shlver: what does that even mean? "founding fathers is a meme name"
sebiyy: TODAY WE'LL BE MAKING SCRAMBLED EGG PASTATHE BEST FOODIt is easy, cheap, good, easy, great, tasty, quick, low-cost, cool, pasta, nice, and tasty
valleyisle: China has no rights jokerd6Gold
Sublimus7: Progress! Keep in mind, the American govt is one of the oldest in the world
shanumbra: hie
MrBankster: you like indica or sativa?
LinhoArecon: France France lol
quickfloor: Middle east ?
orami: Kappa
fulfy: Magna Carta. The US constitution is based on it.
Huskieee: For example the king of sweden has fuck all rights, he is more of a PR person
Number___Nine: if you were Chinese you would have fled to the US
Number___Nine: under H1B
quickfloor: is that right USA using middle east resources to be still a big player in world ? think about like afghanistan or iraq oil stuffs
valleyisle: Kingdom of Hawaii had a constitution until it got overthrew by America I think
Super_saiyan_3: CHINA NUMBA WON
milanx64: mm Interesting
jagger_rsw: It's not good that for me living in Switzerland I must feel I have no rights as opposed to geohot's position in USA
milanx64: I spent time in the Phillipines on a rice farm
Number___Nine: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/996_working_hour_system
soisoisoi: arent there conecentration camps in china?
ykim122: i think you're right. alot of us aren't in China so its hard for us to relate
sebiyy: EU #1
Richardable: Finland number uno
valleyisle: Brainwashing people
hkisthebest: @georgehotz have you ever been to Taiwan?
prafaeltsantos: what........China GOV is so bad that they are making a society based on points....
FargioFarmani: Yess, Switzerland!
dontbeameme: Switzerland is gang gang for war
revolutionist123: how much to find me a girlfriend? @georgehotz
jagger_rsw: Die Schweiz
valleyisle: 🇺🇸 #1
quickfloor: Freedome
Super_saiyan_3: China has a social score so that it can create a decent society
valleyisle: 🇺🇸 🤝 🇨🇭
astr0nils: yall come to Switzerland its lit over here
FargioFarmani: Grüezi i de Schwiez
death_gadget: Financial credit is not the same as Social Credit
iTeQo_: 🇩🇪 #1
Sublimus7: Yeah but your American Credit Sore doesn't change whether or not you can get a flight out of th country
Caene: When I think about America, I don't think "freedom" anymore, honestly.
astr0nils: Salü
whichtom: isn't america just society based on points but its points in a bank acc?
Number___Nine: https://github.com/996icu/996.ICU
quickfloor: Maybe because there is like 1B people in china
jagger_rsw: on the usa - best country on the world - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VMqcLUqYqrs
sebiyy: we live in a society
sebiyy: :)
dontbeameme: America 1984 big brother
quickfloor: No you live in a video game
Number___Nine: Elon lives in the US
milanx64: I agree
Poselsky: Czech republic <
Poselsky: <3
LinhoArecon: you need to ask the Governement to make a big move in china
jagger_rsw: UKraine!
quickfloor: Oh money brokes in middle east
milanx64: Im a proud capitalist
Sublimus7: America is on of the oldest countries in the world, all of Europe' succesfull govts have stemmed from our constitution
VPVP: KKona
Number___Nine: house with an American flag
dontbeameme: Every system. An be broken if not used right
MrBankster: i just want free food and shelter so i can do nothing all day
Super_saiyan_3: capitalism lets the cream rise to the top
jagger_rsw: Swedes don't complain
Poselsky: @Sublimus7 You mean republic right?
st47ik: whats next stream gonna be about George?
Number___Nine: that sounds like Europe lol
myfirstpotato: unregulated capitalism?
Fulk33: but capitalism and only capitalism is not the holy grail either
dontbeameme: Mcdonalds is super cheap
dorkmo: fusion engergy rant
Sublimus7: @Poselsky well just established govt really, not country though that was the wrong word
prafaeltsantos: America...is a little bit fck up...like the prices you pay for education, health services, etc....
shlver: Capitalism has resulted in big pharma monetizing addiction. At one point, there were more opioid prescriptions than the population in some states.
quickfloor: i mean money is power . where ever you go on the earth
milanx64: yeah imo AI might help with a lot of this. At least we could run sims and test ideas and that would be awesome.
Huskieee: Capitalism is he worst economic system, except for all the others
jagger_rsw: But the times are changing wrt to power in capitalism, there was this catchy phrase that 'math men replaced the mad men' - an article in The Economist or so
valleyisle: Crony capitalism
dontbeameme: Manipulated skinny jeans to be cool
grizvok: SQL
FurikuriYugi: Free = No monetary cost but the Work cost goes up
Fulk33: @georgehotz are you part of the yang gang? xD
prafaeltsantos: capitalism is like bureaucracy, there is no better system
st47ik: this simulation is getting more complicated NotLikeThis
whichtom: hard labels aren't necessary
my_curiosity: @georgehotz does reinforcement learning have any practical value in your opinion?
JonnyPew: SeemsGood
Caene: USA have some nice things going for it, but I'm insanely happy I'm not a US citizen.
minmaxy: so you'd like Siwtzerland-like referendums
dontbeameme: Nice save but only can b one
Kyoto_o: followed you on twitch last night but also just clicked on your interview with lex fridman, planning on listening to it
quickfloor: What government on mars would be ?
aPosterior: geez... the title says simplicity..
st47ik: bugs in the simulation
stalys_: the two party system enables that mindset
Kyoto_o: bug in democracy LUL
Fulk33: I feel like beeing in the political sphere everyday and talking only about it makes me sick
3FXX: Is it harmful to leave the charge cable plugged into laptop?
Poselsky: @Huskieee Anyone can complain, come up with solution. I guess you haven't lived in USSR, Third Reich or true monarchy, saying that capitalism is the worst is bad opinion.
Phantomhive_: @3FXX this isnt tech support
MrBankster: can you advise me on how to get out of web dev?
valleyisle: I’m so glad I was born in America emoneyKona
minmaxy: any law that influences all of Switzerland (not just one of 28 cantons) must pass a referndum
st47ik: we need bugfixes Kappa
grizvok: learn new shit
miloeu: capitalism only works as long as there are enough people to be exploited
Mendacii_: TAX IS FREEDOM Kappa
3FXX: @Phantomhive_ sorry i thought it isa
quickfloor: @MrBankster Private session with george
kzawadi: what if one day you come to know/understand that what you have been seen and knowing is not real....will you change?
FSRoosta: Tribalism is inherent in human nature, history documents this quite clearly.
Kyoto_o: how much hours would you say you code throughout the day @georgehotz
Super_saiyan_3: why were u in china for a year? if u already talked about it feel free to skip over this
dontbeameme: don’t pay property tax and see who owns that land
bool3max: emoneyKona
valleyisle: So much things I don’t have to worry about because I was born in America
valleyisle: @bool3max emoneyKona my man
dunehazard: that's a great take on politics, so many things lately we're trying to separate into sides, a vs b, when humans are so complex how can we think every issue is binary
death_gadget: @miloeu Your ignorance is showing with that statement
Sublimus7: Well Idk about Switerland but America is so vast and diverse that policy does need to be local to be effective
Caene: I would be ashamed of the judiciary. How budgets within the government are managed. I would be ashamed of the insane scale of corruption within the government. I would be ashamed of the class differences. I would be ashamed of the infrastructure in parts of the country that shouldn't be looking/feeling like a third world location. Many things, it would bother me.
Huskieee: @Poselsky what that quote essentially says that capitalism is the best we've got, capitalism in its truest form is is shit. Just because other things are way worse doesnt mean capitalism is great
miloeu: @death_gadget ?
bool3max: @valleyisle 5Head erobb viewers
jagger_rsw: When visiting USA for 2 weeks, I got into trouble with some locals in Mountain View, they started shouting at me 'I was born in USA, not like you!'. I didn't know then why it was important when one was born, but Iknow this person one day will run for president or so :)
Super_saiyan_3: i put all my money in Somalian land homie
valleyisle: emoneyL
dontbeameme: Makes sense
st47ik: Africa is fake Kappa
shlver: Capitalism is good at what it's designed to do, the problem comes when government fails to regulate its excesses which is inevitable since the majority of politicians are human and easily corruptible.
Kyoto_o: you are paying the taxes because government institucions are the ones keeping the books
quickfloor: @st47ik is earth flat ?
stalys_: metacorruption
Greaser_1: Hi, from Portugal!
Mendacii_: Africa has chocolate rivers LUL
dontbeameme: Lololol
Poselsky: @Huskieee German people who lived during Third Reich have been doing great. so you might say that for them fascism was best form of government.
Mendacii_: IS not real BTW LUL
Caene: I mean, that said.. I love spending time in very selected places in the US. Northern California is probably one of the most beautiful places in the world. So as a tourist, I'm insanely happy you have these amazing golden chunks.
LinhoArecon: @st47ik why
prafaeltsantos: @Greaser_1 Saudações Compatriota
miloeu: strongly regulated capitalism is the only good system
stalys_: benevolent dictator
st47ik: @LinhoArecon i mean it's being ignored by everyone mostly
Number___Nine: glorious leader
jagger_rsw: But you're guys changing USA into Europe anywayz. More concentrated healthcare insurances, better unemployment benefits with every year.
Poselsky: @georgehotz TRUE
Greaser_1: Olá @prafaeltsantos! Saudações para ti também!
Super_saiyan_3: except for the Supreme Leader
Huskieee: @Poselsky some german people did, not all, most didnt. Look at like saudi arabia or something rn, some people have it really fucking nice, most dont.
quickfloor: Explain what is a bad country ? it's in your opinion
mantissa: yoo whats goin on
SnakeOneMLG: "The best argument against Democracy is a five-minute conversation with the average voter.” - Winston Churchill
milanx64: Isnt that what we a re trying to do with democracy? Vote and put together the optimal dictator.
iTeQo_: How do you guys describe capitalism?
MrBankster: do you recommend going to library and reading books?
grimers: georgehotz, have you used ros during openpilot development?
lidermaury: tomorrow stream theme will be sport
dawgwhisper007: PROGRAMMING
renatobarresi: how do I achieve your level of intelligence?
Mendacii_: Africa don’t have dictators so they aren’t real
prafaeltsantos: a dictator molds a country to hes view, not the view of the people....so i don´t want a single person deciding for me
Super_saiyan_3: i learn about history from reddit comments
st47ik: @Mendacii_ they do tho
orami: What 5 books do you think most heavily contributed to the way you see things
tornix98: do you believe state capitalism can succeed?
Number___Nine: but what is people are dumb rednecks?
Number___Nine: *if
LinhoArecon: I dont thinks so they trying to make you believe is ignored
Poselsky: Rn only the wealthies of the wealthies model the nowadays world. Simple as that.
Kyoto_o: @renatobarresi ahahahahaah
st47ik: maybe
foti_kasparov: @orami Nice question
mikey9988: KKona ? @Number___Nine
quickfloor: There is taylor swift in america , this is why i'm gonna move to usa
dontbeameme: Dumb people are not allowed to make decisions
orami: or rather 5 which single book
shlver: Yes it is lol. Our tax code is literally written by corporate lobbies.
Cal3b123: have you read the dictators handbook?
orami: rather than*
dunehazard: @Number___Nine proper question would be close minded. which can exist on every part of the spectrum of political affiliation
Sublimus7: "The world is rudderless, and that is the scariest fact of the world" - some comic book author i forgot his name
rebuhleiv: what do you think of Joker? have you seen it and is it realistic to apply to America?
LinhoArecon: I mean Africa as everything that the world need @st47ik
prafaeltsantos: i think a i have bigger chances of influence the power driving a country in a democratic government
Number___Nine: dunehazard there are common patterns like being more right-wing, etc...
st47ik: i see
milanx64: lol
dontbeameme: A whole organization of architects said it couldn’t happen
ICAntF331MyFAce: lmao
quickfloor: What american doing in Afghanistan ?
dawgwhisper007: you deserve to be a character on family guy
tornix98: yes state capitalism in china, can they overtake the us economy eventually?
mushumitsi: stop distracting him
st47ik: LUL
grizvok: yes
mushumitsi: we're trying to read about simplicity here
GGGrimmy: The joker ran for president and here we are
dontbeameme: Lolololol
hoffs: avengers is just alternate name for americans
robbsalm: good books to pass linear algebra?
Kyoto_o: how much hours would you say you code throughout the day @georgehotz
mushumitsi: strang's linear algebra
Huskieee: Linear Algebra for dummies Kappa
michalmx2: do you have an opinion of Poland ?
MrBankster: do you think it's smart to working for a big corp?
alphasweetpea: linear is easy
alphasweetpea: Matrixs
mikey9988: just watch the matrix Kappa
dunehazard: @Number___Nine true, but again, common patterns on all sides
jagger_rsw: tried to prove Riemann's hypothesis?
prafaeltsantos: best books to read?
xrealyy: what
st47ik: wear sunglasses and be badass Kappa
robbsalm: well here in Italy linear algebra is more like abstract algebra
robbsalm: like groups and stuff
grizvok: italian linear algebra isnt linear algebra
grizvok: what
Huskieee: how to linear algebra: import numpy as np
dunehazard: @Number___Nine it's hard for humans to not see themselves or their beliefs as wrong
TheRealMast3r: Life's just an Epimenides paradox, what's your thoughts about that geo
robbsalm: thanks bro with that i will pass my exam
Number___Nine: dunehazard imo those people are more easily manipulated
mushumitsi: yw
Number___Nine: I want to live in a colony on mars
pereman2: looking to spend next year as a exchange student in usa (im from spain), should i bring my own bulletproof vest???
tornix98: do you think Artifical Intelligence can help make communism viable because it can plan the ecnomy more effectively than humans ever can?
Number___Nine: although the Internet would suck
mazsociety: social media influencers are the single greatest threat to humanity
SnakeOneMLG: @robbsalm same here, like they told us about matrix on like the 10th lecture, we were just defining vectors spaces using groups and stuff for like 5 weeks
dawgwhisper007: george hotz griffin https://i.redd.it/utvam3ry68q11.jpg
robbsalm: @SnakeOneMLG where you are studying it?
dunehazard: @mazsociety lmao
SnakeOneMLG: @robbsalm CTU in Prague
hkisthebest: https://imgur.com/a/wvQVjzw Ay we popular guys!
dontbeameme: 100% needed
jagger_rsw: koreans believe that a fan runed on at night will suffocate you by throwing away all oxygen from the room - no kidding :)
Number___Nine: lol 1000
orami: can i have that in writing
prafaeltsantos: @pereman2 can i send you a whisper
pereman2: bro living there is so expensive
Germl: can i shoot myself?
Super_saiyan_3: sounds like a deal to me
foti_kasparov: Can I shoot myself?
grimers: is george a social media influencer and can we truste him 🤔
dontbeameme: 100% crips and bloods every corner
pereman2: might go to polonia
mushumitsi: sounds like a business opportunity
Huskieee: So walking out with a sign saying "please shoot me, ill give you $500" doesnt count?
pereman2: sure
MrBankster: you gonna get shot for sure now
alphasweetpea: 350
Caene: Caene subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 1 month streak!
Number___Nine: can I shoot him and we split 50-50
tornix98: do you think Artifical Intelligence can help make communism viable because it can plan the ecnomy more effectively than humans ever can?
shlver: Okay, I'll make some pamphlets and flyers and post them in inner city neighborhoods and racist small towns
Caene: 👍
valleyisle: It’s crazy how people think mass shooting are just happening everyday in the USA jokerd6Gold
YouPowerRush: h e h e
dontbeameme: yoink
Sublimus7: @tornix98 look into a Resource Based Economy, basically the same idea developed in the 70's
Caene: LUL
Number___Nine: new hightech bulletprof vests startup
dontbeameme: Lololol
orami: XDDDDDDDDD
dontbeameme: Yep
MrBankster: car crashes scare the shit out of me
YouPowerRush: haha
valleyisle: True
mazsociety: someone in a facebook thread for my city was asking about buying a bulletproof backpack for their kid for school NotLikeThis
stalys_: ban vapes too Kappa
foti_kasparov: I think we should call it Tesla
smurfd0: that stuff sounds great ;)
Super_saiyan_3: Saudi Arabia already thoughtof this by taking women off the roads
grizvok: Total loss of control
stalys_: just don't fly on a Boeing LUL
dontbeameme: USA biggest developments , computer tech and language
jagger_rsw: but on a more serious note, it was so sad when I learned that (some?) US schools kids are learning small poems about 'school lock downs' to remember how to behave in case of troubles
quickfloor: That would be the future , i would buy it . we can name it openpilot or something
Germl: if (car.willCrash)
valleyisle: Planes are way safer than cars
FSRoosta: trivialising gun deaths in the US seems like not a good plan.
rebuhleiv: what do you think of the recent news arount Waymo? seems they are leading
quickfloor: LUL
Number___Nine: we had this "active shooter" training at work here in the UK once, that was super weird
orami: CX
hoffs: but plane crash is like almost certain death, car crash can just like handicap you which is imo worse than being dead
grizvok: LOL
dontbeameme: Not me, some kid
MrBankster: yup i remember those
Number___Nine: Soviet bombs are coming
quickfloor: i thouth you were nerd in school
Sublimus7: @hoffs apparently that's not the case, more surivors of airplane crashes than you think
jagger_rsw: Putin stronk
iTeQo_: Anyone buying Saudi Aramco shares after their IPO?
TheRealMast3r: So that's life in USA. Nothing happens in France
valleyisle: @hoffs Yea but plane crashes are rare jokerd6Gold
Super_saiyan_3: did u go to college?
tornix98: do you think Artifical Intelligence can help make communism viable because it can plan the ecnomy more effectively than humans ever can?
shlver: "cool in hs" nobody was cool in hs, we were all dipshits
hoffs: @Sublimus7 depends on the crashes, if its bad youre likely to die, if its meh-ish then sure
hkisthebest: @georgehotz are we programming or not??
dontbeameme: @iteqo_ When they ipo
JonnyPew: So clowns are cool? LUL
valleyisle: @therealmast3r Except terrorist attacks jokerd6Gold
TheRealMast3r: Statistical stand point require to not compare different distribution. You missed that subject at school or what :/
dontbeameme: I think in survival terms, if I have xy food, you want that food
quickfloor: it's really hard to know how world working
rebuhleiv: what do you think about the current development of WAYMO?
ICAntF331MyFAce: vineClown
exclamationpointe: This guy talking bout politics meanwhile he’s missing pen ile skin
mazsociety: m (A) rx (I) sm
Number___Nine: While selling devices with schematics was a common practice everywhere, you are, interestingly, correct. The USSR had the government organization, GosFAP(ГосФАП, National Fund of Algorithms and Programs), which was enforcing sharing of code in the country. I recall reading in some memoirs that it effectively shunted software development as you had to register any software with it and it involved printing source code, filling forms and traveling to the physical location of the office and interact
quickfloor: LUL
Kyoto_o: whats the most interesting book in your opinion from that list that's popping out slightly @georgehotz
valleyisle: Do you think the world relatively gets better over time ?
YouPowerRush: yee
TheRealMast3r: 100% agree
whichtom: ye
exclamationpointe: @valleyisle not for the average being hell nah
jagger_rsw: and DMCA
minmaxy: RIP pharma industry
dontbeameme: long live russia for tetris
Sublimus7: Oof thats a hard sell
foti_kasparov: cbrahNA
ProfessorMagikarp0: george 2020
quickfloor: GEORGE RULES
dawgwhisper007: RuleFive
tornix98: if you remove intellectual property there would be no incentives for creative destruction
exclamationpointe: This guy is 2% as woke as the kids will be in 30 years
SKPTCL: what will incentivize pharmacy companies to invest billions into new drugs if they cant patent?
exclamationpointe: If ml doesnt get us enslaved first
dawgwhisper007: no copyright seriously?
Megaliskuu: how do u feel abiut Edward Snowden
dontbeameme: No no the corruption is people hiding money off shore lol
ICAntF331MyFAce: LUL
Number___Nine: we've gotten sidetracked from learning category theory again, lol
YouPowerRush: DIE DIE DIE
valleyisle: Just started reading permanent record by Edward Snowden
tornix98: if you remove intellectual property laws there would be no incentives for any creative destruction
kungfudog2012: whens chicken tendies
dontbeameme: Real curruption is aimbot in FPS
Kyoto_o: what you on about, give me some :)
YouPowerRush: got em
Number___Nine: category theory and chill
quickfloor: is he gonna wash his hands ???
ProfessorMagikarp0: jailbreaking george with intellectual property laws LUL
quickfloor: i'm nervus
exclamationpointe: lme send u a website url @georgehotz
quickfloor: 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 is the best private key i have ever seen
Number___Nine: quickfloor you have to conserve water, bro
jagger_rsw: But you haven't responded to the most important distraction topic: Star Trek or Star Wars?
hkisthebest: @georgehotz where do you live?
jagger_rsw: tru dat
quickfloor: i mean i like logan paul
Caene: JJ'
Number___Nine: hkisthebest San Diego
thomasmas: SeemsGood
Caene: JJ's best work is probably Felicity LUL
crashnk: des fr?
exclamationpointe: @georgehotz oeis.org
dontbeameme: go fund me
revolutionist123: plz do it
Caene: I loved that show, no joke
revolutionist123: george for god to save the world
crashnk: taourImam taourImam taourImam
vlntnstts: <3
dontbeameme: she cute
YouPowerRush: tap tap tap
revolutionist123: @georgehotz dm her
dyslexicat: felicity LUL
Number___Nine: is Alex (or Alice) gonna come today?
oksan309: Can u describe Donald Trump in one word ?
DevoE444: i dont think its fap time hotz Kappa
quickfloor: an alone man
Number___Nine: we talk only about Donald Duck
jagger_rsw: So maybe about Angela Merkel
oksan309: LUL
exclamationpointe: Go to oeis.org and give ur thoughts
orami: LUL
JonnyPew: You figure people would be tired of talking about him.
crashnk: winnie the poh ahah
quickfloor: talk about George W. Bush
foti_kasparov: Best ML Beginner book?
revolutionist123: LUL
quickfloor: by by George W. Bush
dyslexicat: talking about trump monkaS
Ya_mums_granny: LUL
JonnyPew: That's a winner.
Number___Nine: russian bots
exclamationpointe: programming cant be that hard if this guy is important in the field lmao embarassment
foti_kasparov: Controversial
quickfloor: is trump a media guy ?
smurfd0: hes a good distraction ;)
asaalgk: wait but does that correlate with the trends of category theory
hoffs: trump is huge media guy
Caene: @exclamationpointe 🤔
mazsociety: we could really use a russian president
dyslexicat: exclamationpointe FeelsWeirdMan
JonnyPew: lUL
orami: 🔨 GET HIM
Number___Nine: get baaaannneddd
dyslexicat: ban him FeelsGoodMan
Phantomhive_: LUL
zenkai_oogway: monkaS
dontbeameme: white privilege trump
mikey9988: LUL
Number___Nine: subscribe fast
ProfessorMagikarp0: luniBan
7Locrian7: 7Locrian7 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months! i didnt mean to sub again, this was an accident
YouPowerRush: exposed
0om4ar: LUL
orami: happy little accident
FargioFarmani: You look like a fool
quickfloor: No insult , be smart
Caene: I'm too much of a pussy to insult you, even though I'm a subscriber LUL
korede360: What chair is that @georgehotz ?
vlntnstts: Привет, как дела? :)
Number___Nine: korede360 a $5000 one
JonnyPew: Offence is taken, not given Kappa
foti_kasparov: Can you make that accident on me please? Im poor
hkisthebest: how often do you stream, cause I am considering subscribing
revolutionist123: that reminded me my life
quickfloor: We only talk about fundamental things in this channel
eax_ebx: how about Ukraine?
SKPTCL: @korede360 sayl chair
smurfd0: 'vundle' is a good vim plugin manager fyi
prafaeltsantos: talk about the bed, that is a good looking bed
Kyoto_o: @hkisthebest check the vods and time between them
dontbeameme: fake chair
Number___Nine: SUBLEQ sounds like an AArch32 instruction, tbh
Number___Nine: oh it is
alxhotel: having the bed in the kitchen is the best protip I have seen
quickfloor: History
Number___Nine: RISC-V need stable extentions
eax_ebx: geohot have 2 chairs... You know that joke?)
Number___Nine: E(
Number___Nine: E9
jagger_rsw: You must love POWERPC since you spent lots of time breaking PS :)
exclamationpointe: rokobasilisk
Kyoto_o: do you have some general tips for people for upcoming programmers
Caene: @georgehotz what happened to your prospecting career starting Unity VR programming streams? LUL
Kyoto_o: jesus, my brain lagged
quickfloor: Why AVR cheaps are dead ?
Kyoto_o: you get the point
Number___Nine: RISC-V has a lot of draft extentions, but they aren't stable yet
oksan309: Have u studied control theory?
zoki_macola: https://trends.google.com/trends/explore?date=all&geo=US&q=/m/02z0lb8
Number___Nine: LIBRE people started looking at POWER instead for their GPU because they need vFPU
Caene: Sorry FeelsBadMan
jagger_rsw: PowerPC stronk
orami: ahahaha thanks for the fun though!
tornix98: !uptime
thomasmas: BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump
JonnyPew: Welcome to the internet
mazsociety: quick guys, donate to bribe him into streaming
dontbeameme: ok we be good
Kyoto_o: don't read the chat 😡
dontbeameme: We will be good
ProfessorMagikarp0: daddy george doesnt love us FeelsBadMan
dontbeameme: BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump
jagger_rsw: or, to program AI in Risc-V
foti_kasparov: Thanks George
Caene: Peace!
doctrinacuriosa: What are you reading?
MrBankster: how much money?
SKPTCL: pce
Caene: Thanks for the stream
Number___Nine: please subscribe
thomasmas: BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump
sk84uhlivin: BibleThump
xrealyy: whats your plan for the rest of the day
Number___Nine: quick
gusfrehse: finally
SnakeOneMLG: by by <3
quickfloor: Do you love trolls too ?
dontbeameme: Daddy no
FurikuriYugi: Peace
zenkai_oogway: BibleThump
mazsociety: All hail Lord Hotz
oksan309: U get distracted easily LUL
lidermaury: BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump
HugoDerruci3: peace
orami: <3
prafaeltsantos: nooooo
Caene: Bye bye!
foti_kasparov: BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump
leknar: people pay to watch you read books man
LaheyFPS: BibleThump ABUSE
neca420: we aren't worthy FeelsBadMan
FargioFarmani: he gone
trustME_SC2: Bye have a nice one
Number___Nine: lmao
tris790: BibleThump
dontbeameme: BibleThump BibleThump
prafaeltsantos: CIAO
YouPowerRush: ree
mushumitsi: good job people
Jannnik: BibleThump
data_day_life: Read In Peace
Glymse: BibleThump
mushumitsi: you made him leave
Number___Nine: that was a funny stream for once
Kyoto_o: book name?
spicethyme: Our fault FeelsBadMan
prafaeltsantos: BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump 4Head 4Head
exclamationpointe: Cringe
xrealyy: guys lets go apex or minecraft
prafaeltsantos: StinkyCheese StinkyCheese StinkyCheese
FargioFarmani: book: http://us.metamath.org/downloads/metamath.pdf
foti_kasparov: Roblox it is
konradmad: george hotz more ljke georgebotz